[Music]
[Música]
Ok here we Go
Ok here we Go
the here perform for you if you know the
the here perform for you if you know the
words you can Jo put your hands together
words you can Jo put your hands Together
ifap as we take you through this monkey [
ifap as we take you through this monkey
Music]
[Música]
rap Donkey come
rap Donkey come
d
d
Donkey Donkey He's the leader of the
Donkey Donkey He's the leader of the
bunch you know him well He's Finally back to Kick
bunch you know him well He's Finally
some his Coconut gum can Fire
back to Kick some his Coconut gum can
And sps If he shoots you It's gna hurt
Fire And sps If he shoots you It's gna
He's bigger faster and stronger too
hurt He's bigger faster and stronger too
He's the First member of the K
He's the First member of the K
Crew Donkey
Crew Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
H Donkey
H Donkey
Kong  Donkey Kong is H Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is H
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong got so Listen up to She can shrink
Kong got so Listen up to She can shrink
size to her She quick and need to can
size to su her She quick and need to can
FL through the air and Climb up tre if
FL through the air and Climb up tre if
you choose her not choose wrong with the
you choose her not choose wrong with the
skip and a H She's One
skip and a H She's One
cool Donkey
cool Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
[Music]
[Música]
dkey Kong
dkey
Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
Kong Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
he has no gra has Face
he has no
when he needs to touch his Arms out [
when he need toch his Arms out
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Hello  afternoons horny grandpa how happy he is very happy [Music] pom Bom pom bom bom pom
Buenas tardes abuelo cachón cómo está
pom bom bom bom pom [
pom Bom pom bom bom pom pom bom bom
Music]
[Música]
Bom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
Bom pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam pam
p yosi Pam p p pam [Music] p [Music] pom Bom [Music]
p yosi Pam p p pam
pam pam pam pam pam pam p p P [
pam pam pam pam pam pam p p P
what month of
qué mes de
December what month of December is
diciembre qué mes de diciembre está
this family doing Look eh They just
haciendo este familia Mira eh Me acaban
gave me a joy they just gave me two
de dar una alegría me acaban de dar dos
joys
alegría
okay Tomorrow it will probably render
vale Ya mañana se renderiza seguramente
at night Now The
por la noche Ya El
rewind Okay Julio Yes now I'll tell you
rewind Bueno Julio Sí ahora os cuento lo
about nimmu who wants to close my Twitter account
de nimmu que me quiere cerrar la cuenta
man very strong
tío muy fuerte
eh there was one there was a streamer there was a
eh había una había un streamer había un
streamer who I thought was going to
streamer que me creía que me iba a
leave me stranded in
dejar tirado en
the  that I thought he was going to fail us
el que me me creía que nos iba a fallar
I thought he was going to let us fail and it wasn't
me creía que nos iba a dejar fallar y no
going to be in the rewind but he just
iba a salir en el rewind pero me acaba
sent me the clip and I
de mandar el clip y me ha
loved it a kiss Lucia Hey and I just went
encantado un beso Lucía Oye y me acabo
to look at the members and we are
de meter a mirar los miembros y estamos
13 members away from reaching 5000 no
a 13 miembros de llegar a los 5000 no O
So we are going to reach 5000
sea que vamos a llegar hoy a los 5000
members today hosa but we are not going to finish
miembros hosa pero ya no vamos a acabar
the year with 6000 no way not in the
el año con 6000 ni de coña no en la
salsería
salsería
no I don't think no I don't
no no creo
think we are going to reach 6000
no no creo que vayamos a llegar a 6000
before the end of the year it won't be a [ __ ]
antes de acabar el año no sera una [__]
fads ima
fads ima
not as if art the Twitter account was
no como si arte la cuenta de Twitter le
going to take it away F cheer up no but look
fuera a quitar lo F nimo no pero mira yo
in the physical I have not given my opinion eh
en el físico no he opinado eh
sincerely apart it is that no physical
sinceramente aparte es que no ni físico
or anything It's that I was not giving my opinion of
ni nada Es que yo no estaba opinando de
nimu at all because I have my thing
nimu para nada porque tengo mi movida
with delox and messing with the girlfriend to see
con delox y meterme con la novia a ver
I think it was like no I don't know it makes me
Me parece que era como no no sé me
uncomfortable okay but yes it is true that
incomoda vale pero sí que es verdad que
the girl does not stop every time every
es que la tía no para cada vez que cada
time that  has an interaction with me or
vez que tiene una interacción conmigo o
comes to my account for something is to
viene a mi cuenta para algo es para
insult
insultar
man is to insult and it is like it has I am not at
tío es para insultar y es como tiene no
all you
te estoy nada
guys it is being
chicos está siendo
cinema it is being a [ __ ] madness
cine está siendo una [__] locura
eh Seriously eh Maybe I am
eh En serio eh A lo mejor os Estoy hype
too hyped eh I don't know if I am too hyped
demasiado eh No sé si os Estoy hype
but what you are going to nothing or rather what You are going
pero lo que vais nada o sea lo que Vais
to see on the 28th
a ver el 28
what You are going to see on the 28th man
lo que Vais a ver el 28
man what video what video what video I can't
tío tío qué vídeo qué vídeo qué vídeo no
stop Watching the scenes man a kiss Aide
paro de Ver las escenas tío un beso Aide
Eh I can't stop Watching the scenes that we have
Eh no paro de Ver las escenas que hemos
done this is like this or is it like this man I mean it's like this
hecho esto es así o es así tío o sea es
actually of course it's like this and I Well I
así en realidad claro es así y yo Bueno
always take it like this but it is like this of course it is like this
siempre lo cojo así pero es así claro es
r it would be like this
así r sería así
[Music]
[Música]
em move it forward to today grandpa no no no no
em adelántala para hoy abuelo no no no
no how am I going to move it forward to today
no no cómo lo voy a adelantar para hoy
[ __ ] it's not finished they are closing they are
[__] no está terminado están cerrando
Finishing reviewing
están Terminando de repasar
but it's that it is one scene after another Pin
pero es que es una escena tras otra Pin
Pin Pin I mean it's that he is very handsome
Pin Pin o sea es que es guapísimo
man no Pacheco No I already know that it is April
tío no Pacheco No ya sé que es el Día de
Fool's Day the 28th I already know the day of the
los inocentes el 28 ya lo sé el día del
premiere  it was actually uh the day of the
estreno era el en realidad eh el día del
premiere was the 26th it was tomorrow what happens is
extreno era el 26 era mañana lo que pasa
that since we got our fingers caught a little bit, let's
que como nos pillamos un poquillo los
see, we could have had it
dedos no a ver se podría haber tenido A
Maybe tomorrow because actually
lo mejor mañana porque en realidad
Tomorrow the video is going to be rendered and
Mañana se va a renderizar el vídeo ya lo
what happens is that the the truth is that we would
que pasa es que la la la verdad que nos
like we wanted to take a couple of days
gustaría queríamos [__] un par de días
like that of of of
así de
space so that to leave the
de de de hueco para que para dejar el
video scheduled it is okay for the
vídeo programado vale que estuviera el
video to be uploaded to the channel for at least
vídeo subido en en el canal por lo menos
one day no at least the video to be there for
un día no por lo menos que esté el vídeo
a day a day and a half uploaded to the channel
un día un día y medio sub en el canal
in case a copyright jumps in case there is
por si salta copyright por si hay
anything There is a lot of music there is a
cualquier cosa Hay mucha música que hay
lot of
mucha
music then also one of the girls
música luego también una de las chicas
uh who sings has copyright one of the
eh que cantan tiene copyright una de las
artists who sings has copyright they
artistas que canta tiene copyright nos
have to take it away from us
lo tienen que quitar en
anyway it's crazy eh You're going to freak out man you do
fin es una locura eh Vais a flipar tío
n't expect it Hey what
es que no os lo esperáis Oye qué
goal do we set today now that Fran has
objetivo ponemos hoy ahora que Fran ha
made a super chat what goal
hecho un super chat qué objetivo
could we
podríamos
set Good night handsome gentleman
poner Buenas noches caballero apuesto
I hope the king of gossip had
Espero que el rey del salseo haya pasado
a happy time Thank you for your work
una felic baidat Gracias por tu trabajo
Javi red heart you are a
Javi corazón rojo eres un
crack Dallas appears let's see I  I think that I
crack aparece Dallas a ver yo creo que
think that no eh I think that it's not going to come
yo creo que no eh yo creo queas no va a
out in any way, maybe in
salir ni de
56 months that you don't burn eh
coña tal 56 meses qu tu no te quemas eh
Let's see,
A ver
what I do have to tell you is that let's
yo lo que sí que tengo que deciros es
see with all humility,
que a ver con toda la humildad
obviously
evidentemente
No, it's not going to be up to the editing level
No no va a est a la altura de montaje A
Maybe Alex is cool I mean, I don't
lo mejor que Alex molón no O sea no
have those means and those resources
tengo esos medios y esos recursos
and
e
[Music]
[Música]
but but but but but but but
pero pero pero pero pero pero
for me it's cinema, I mean for me It's
pero para mí es cine o sea para mí Está
very well done, it's very well spun, it's very, it's very, it's very, very, very
muy bien hecho está muy bien hilado está
worked on the scenes have a lot of
currados las escenas tienen mucha
quality, I mean, for me it's cinema, the
calidad o sea para mí está para mí cine
truth is, you know, for me it's the [ __ ] [ __ ]
la verdad sabes que para mí es la [__]
Regarding the cameos and the winks, I'm
[__] Respecto a los cameos y los guiños
not going to tell you, obviously, I don't know, you
no os lo voy a decir evidentemente yo
already know, no, but I've
que sé ustedes ya sabéis no pero yo le
asked everyone for a scene, I've
he pedido a todo el mundo una escena le
asked everyone for a cameo
he pedido a todo el mundo un cameo al
that I haven't asked because it already has
que no se lo he pedido porque ya tiene
too much presence, okay.
demasiada presencia vale
But there's a surprise, obviously no, there are no
Pero hay sorpresa claro evidentemente no
surprises, there's no cinema, there's cinema,
no hay sorpresas no hay cine hay cine
man, I mean, it's crazy It's not that you're
tío o sea es que es de loco Es que no es
not going to  let's see there are
que no lo Vais a ver venir hay escenas
exciting scenes the youtubers rewind are
emocionantes los youtubers rewind son
very bad you must be a big fan of some of
muy malos deb ser muy fan de alguno de
those youtubers for you to like it but
esos youtubers para que te guste pero
this one is
este es
mine elbel and uncle shen r will appear no way no way
mío aparecerán elbel y el tío shen r ni
and Dallas even less what contact do
coña y el Dallas menos qué contacto
I have with those
tengo yo con esos
Random no but listen to me too much or I mean You're
Random no pero escuchame demasiado o sea
going to freak out eh a You're going to freak out It's that
Vais a flipar eh a Vais a flipar Es que
every time I see a trailer every time I
yo cada vez que veo un avance cada vez
see a new touch and [ __ ]
que veo un toque nuevo e tomar por culo
this This has gotten out of hand it has
esto Esto se nos ha ido de las manos
gotten out of hand Hey what
se nos ha ido de las manos Oye qué
objective do we
objetivo
set serene had cam let's see man don't
ponemos serene tuvo cam a ver tío no
ask don't ask this one comes out the
preguntéis no preguntéis este sale el
other one comes out I who know who do you
otro Sale yo yo que sé ustedes quién
think is in it
creéis que
who do you think is in it
sale quién creéis que sale
this will be the new rewind I hope it's for
este será el nuevo rewind Ojalá sea para
a wider audience and not gossip let's see
un público más amplio y no salseo a ver
if I can tell you the truth
si os digo la verdad
eh I dropped a couple of
eh se me cayeron un par de
scenes I dropped a couple of scenes
escenas se me cayeron un par de escenas
that weren't gossip but were from
que no eran de salseo sino que eran de
other communities
otras comunidades
and there are many communities on YouTube No,
e hay muchas comunidades en YouTube No
me when I have criticized r it has
yo cuando he cuando he criticado el r
always been not from the stick no no but
siempre ha sido no del palo no no pero
not here  everyone comes out I don't know what I don't
aquí no sale todo el mundo no sé qué no
know how much no Eh I don't know
sé cuánto no Eh Yo que sé comunidad
mechanical community no there's no one from the
mecánica no no hay nadie de la comunidad
mechanical community El poncito has given away 50 with
mecánica El poncito ha regalado 50 con
that we've already passed 5000
eso ya hemos pasado sobrados los 5000
family members let's see if we get
miembros familia vamos a ver si llegamos
to 6000 before it ends of course let's
a los 6000 antes de que acabe claro a
see there are communities that don't come out there are no
ver hay Hay comunidades que no salen no
communities that don't come out it's that the
hay comunidades que no salen es que el
ru at first was for gossip an r of
ru en un principio era de salseo un r
mine What happens is that I Li we
mío Lo que pasa que me
started working on it I don't know
Li empezamos a trabajar en él no sé hace
a month and a half ago two months I don't remember and
un mes y medio dos meses no me acuerdo y
then it was mom's turn from here I ca
entonces le ha tocado a mamá de se aquí
n't believe it it was mom's turn
no me lo puedo creer le ha tocado mamá
from here the member I can't
de se aquí el miembro no me lo puedo
believe it Well she won't have noticed tomorrow ent we'll tell her let's
creer Pues ni se habrá dado cuenta maana
see The Movida is that of
ent se lo decimos a ver La Movida es que
course me me things were coming to me
claro me me se me fueron ocurriendo
things were coming to me no
cosas se me fueron ocurriendo cosas no
oh I'm going to ask this one I don't know what I'm
ay le voy a pedir a este no sé qué le
going to ask the other one I don't know how much I'm going to
voy a pedir al otro no sé cuánto voy a
go record with I don't know who And then of
ir a grabar con no sé quién Y entonces
course eh
claro eh A lo
Maybe maybe we've had to
mejor a lo mejor hemos tenido que
lower it a little bit  Let's see, in
rebajar un poquito de A ver es que en
reality it's not like I've
realidad tampoco es como que haya
lowered it let's see what happens is that you
rebajado a ver lo que pasa es que tú
know how so many youtubers collaborate Well maybe I
sabes como colaboran tantos youtubers
've also tried to
Pues a lo mejor he intentado también
lower it a little bit so that it doesn't feel
rebajar un poquito que no le siente nada
bad to
mal a
anyone who then tells me oh you put me
nadie que luego me diga ah me has metido
in this video where nobody reproaches
en este vídeo donde se no se increpa
anyone obviously
nadie evidentemente
no I don't know it's funny you do
no no sé es gracioso
n't realize how difficult it is to
no te das cuenta de lo difícil que es
include all the communities until you
incluir todas las comunidades hasta que
actually try to make a rewi already already
realmente intentas hacer un rewi ya ya
but it's that
pero es
I also thought when
que es que tampoco Pensaba yo cuando
we started that the r was going to be like this
empezábamos que el r iba a ser así
eh but well let's see what
eh pero bueno a ver vamos a ver qué
happens let's see what happens The
sale vamos a ver qué sale Yo lo único
only thing that I would ask of life and
que lo único que sí pediría a la vida y
the YouTube algorithm at least that it does
al algoritmo de YouTube por lo menos que
n't keep me with 3000 visits
no se me vaya a quedar con 3000 visiti
40000 visits can you imagine but not for nothing
40000 visi te imaginas pero no por nada
but because [ __ ] I've made a lot of
sino porque [__] llevo muchísimo
sacrifices not only in what we're
sacrificio ya no solamente en lo que
working on but man there will have to be
estamos trabajando sino que hombre habrá
money for everyone who
que tendrán que cobrar todos los que
is working they will have to I will have to
están trabajando tendrán
amortize the trips that
que tendré que amortizar los viajes que
I've made no eh I will have to hom and about
he hecho no eh tendré que hom y sobre
all every day that I've been without
todo todos los días que he estado sin
uploading videos and
subir vídeos y
stuff you know I don't know it will cost me
cosas sabes no sé me saldrá pagar
at least 500,000 man I wish
seguramente al menos 500000 hombre Ojalá
being
el ser
alone had 500,000 views but man
solo tener 500000 visitas pero hombre yo
if I got 100,000 200,000 I'd be
si me cogiera 100000 200000 estara
happy at least
feliz por lo menos
not the 24th was Franco
no el 24 fue de Franco
de
de
Arón I'll play it on loop for you
arón yo lo reproduzco bucle por ti
man Well look what I would
hombre Pues mira yo lo que os
appreciate with 200,000 the expense is covered
agradecería con 200000 se cubre el gasto
man I don't think 200,000 is covered
hombre no creo que con 200000 se cubre
the expense good hanger but at least it
el gasto buena percha pero por lo menos
's a figure that would be
es una cifra que estaría
good I'm telling you if I got at
bien ya te digo con que coja por lo
least 100,000 I wouldn't be
menos 100.000 no me me quedaría
calm man if it stayed at 50,000
tranquilo hombre si se quedara en 50.000
views 40,000 views the truth is it would
visitas 40.000 visitas la verdad que
be a stick
sería un palo
eh it would be a
eh sería un
stick some big elite youtuber comes out
palo sale algún youtuber tocho de la
What do you think
élite tú Qué crees
extor What do you
extor tú Qué
think the discussion appears Of course
crees aparece la tertulia Por supuesto
not Game Boy When does the video come out Javi on the
no Game Boy Cuándo sale el vídeo Javi el
28th at  8 in the afternoon there are a lot of people
28 a las 8 de la tarde hay mucha gente
who think it's an April Fool's joke,
que se piensa que es una inocentada
dude, plex comes out Of course
tío sale plex Por supuesto que
not, let's see what would be good Is that
no a ver lo que lo que estaría bien Es
everyone shared it and
que que todo el mundo lo compartiera y
that's
eso
worth everyone sharing
vale que todo el mundo lo compartiera en
the link on Twitter
Twitter el enlace en todas
everywhere let's see, I understand that since
partes a ver yo entiendo que que al ser
the
mío el
rewi is mine, well, no, it's not going to have it, not
rewi pues no no va a tener no va a
everyone is going to react and things like that, you don't
reaccionar todo el mundo y esas cosas no
appear in it
sales
Of course not either,
tú Por supuesto que tampoco
the people who react to it on Twitter wouldn't
no la gente que lo reaccione por twit no
be a problem, man No, I can't
daría problema hombre No yo no puedo
be in a live show but but they
estar en un directo pero pero ellos
can react, yours are mine, of course, man
pueden reaccionar vos míos claro hombre
I imagine that the gossip channels will
Yo me imagino que los canales de salseo
see it No, I imagine that
si si lo verán No yo me imagino que el
Chu and these people will
Chu y esta gente si lo
see it but but no, not as many people as
verán pero pero no no tanta gente como
react to the albulón, no I mean, I
reacciona al al de almolón no O sea yo
don't think it's going to be put on
no creo que se ponga
But well, but
Pero bueno pero
well, he will be there of course,
bueno el estará por supuestísimo que
the 180 km/h guy won't appear, I don't
no sale el chico de los 180 km hora no
know who he
sé quién
is, cre much a, it's
es cre much
uni, it's
a es uní es
cinema, it's cinema Look, outside, joking, I'm not
cine es cine Mira ya fuera coña no os
going to tell you, the people who collaborate,
voy a decir la gente que colabora
obviously no  I'm going to tell you okay you
evidentemente no os la voy a decir vale
'll find it in the
os la iréis encontrando en el
premiere but it's cinema, I mean the editing, it
extreno pero es cine o sea la edición a
seems to me it seems like they're
m me parece a m parece que están
making a [ __ ]
haciendo que están haciendo una [__] una
gem, a little princess appears of course not
joya sale princesita por supuesto que no
that you're making a [ __ ] gem in the
que estás haciendo una [__] joya en la
editing okay there's a lot of music okay there are a lot of
edición vale hay mucha música vale hay
musical scenes there are
muchas escenas musicales
many, many cameos
hay muchísimos muchísimos cameos
many
muchísimos
gas there are let's
gas
say three animation companies
hay digamos tres empresas de animación
okay well two are two are animators
vale bueno dos son dos son animadores
who make animated drawings and that and
que hacen dibujillos animados Y eso y
one is a company that makes one that
una es una empresa que que hace una que
works in cinema and stuff like that okay And
trabaja en cine y esas cosas vale Y
then there are a few
entonces ha hay hay unas cuantas de
animations and special effects that are
animaciones y de efectos especiales que
so cool I think that those parts might be
hombre tn chulo yo creo que esas partes
seen by streamers
sí que puede que la vean los streamers
eh I think there are some parts that are
eh yo creo que hay unas partes que están
made with special effects and I think
hechas con con efectos especiales y creo
that And I think that they might
que Y creo que eso sí puede que lo
react a lot to that Frank appears a lot Of
reaccionen mucho mucho sale Frank Por
course not
supuesto que no tampoco
Disney either Nick and Cartoon
Disney Nick y Cartoon
Network let's see I would love to show you something
Network a ver Me encantaría poneros algo
but of course I prefer not I prefer not to
pero claro prefiero No prefiero no
spoil and and that suddenly you start
spoilear y y que de repente lo vayáis
seeing everything
viendo todo
release a trailer because the truth is that  I would have
lanza tráiler pues la verdad que me
liked the truth is that we would have
gustado la verdad que nos hubiera
liked Look,
gustado Mira
the idea was this Sunday to have
em la idea era este domingo haber hecho
done a live with Fran eh To
un haber hecho un directo con Fran eh
announce the map okay What
Para para anunciar el mapa vale Lo que
happens is that the map has been delayed a few
pasa que el mapa se ha [__] unos
days and I think that we will announce the map I do
días y creo que el mapa lo anunciaremos
n't know maybe next week I
No sé a lo mejor la semana que viene me
imagine do you think it will end up
imagino crees que se termine
becoming an
convirtiendo en algo
annual thing man and Luis if he gives me a million
anual hombre y Luis si me da un millón
visits or
de visit o
two yes I can consider it
dos sí que me lo puedo plantear
but I don't think so can you imagine Can you imagine I do
pero no creo te
n't know let's see I do think that
imaginas no sé a ver yo sí creo que
when they
cuando lo
see it there is very little that they haven't
vean es que hay muy poco que que no
told me no eh There are
hayan que me hayan dicho que no eh Hay
very few I can count on the fingers of
muy pocos puedo contar con los dedos de
one hand a kiss from the people that I
una mano un beso de la gente que a la
have asked
que le he pedido
something from the people that I have asked
algo de la gente a la que le he pedido
something from there are very few that have not done it for me
algo hay muy poco que no que no me lo
Eh there is very little that I think has not done it for me
Eh hay muy poco que creo que no me lo
So I think that when
hayan hecho Entonces yo creo que cuando
they see it they are going to say
lo vean van a decir
wow this was
[__] esto estaba
cool tell those who told you to
chulo dil los que te dijeron
be a
ser
spoiler no est no
spoiler no est no
no da ig
no da ig
later later we will
después después hablamos nosotros lo
react no obviously
reaccionaremos no evidentemente
no we will react
no nosotros lo reaccionaremos
no let's see but it's that you are  putting a
no a ver pero es que me estáis poniendo
name of pure Random also
nombre de puro Random también
eh You're putting people who don't
eh Me estáis poniendo gente que ni
even belong to anything this year
siquiera pertenece a nada de este año
also let's see man a
también a ver tío un
re No you can't
re No tú no lo puedes
react I think I'll react to
reaccionar yo creo yo lo reaccionar para
go comment on it not to go comment on
ir comentaros lo no para ir comentando
your your scenes Oh look well we
vuestra vuestras escenas Ay mira pues
did this
esto lo hicimos
Here I also tell you that there are people who that do
Aquí también os digo que hay hay gente
n't come out But also
que que que no sale Pero también por
because of me eh There are people who don't come out
culpa mía eh Hay gente que no sale
Because
Porque
and I have been like very hasty to ask for
e yo he ido como muy precipitado a pedir
things sometimes also eh
algunas veces las cosas también eh daros
realize that suddenly as we were
cuenta que de repente conforme ibamos
squaring up here it would be good for me if this one
cuadrando aquí me vendría bien que este
told me I don't know how much you know and maybe he
me dijera no sé cuánto sabes y a lo
was on a trip maybe I don't know
mejor estaba de viaje a lo mejor no sé
what it is that there are many that I have
qué es que hay muchos a los que se lo he
asked in the last last week
pedido en la en la última semana pasada
and then they are maybe on a trip I don't
y entonces están a lo mejor de viaje no
know
sé
where Yes man of course memes yes memes yes
dónde Sí hombre claro memes sí memes sí
the memes do come out of
los memes sí salen
course I say that you release it in a
claro yo digo que lo saques en un
live we see it all together live
directo lo vemos todos juntos en directo
man it is a premiere it is
hombre es un extreno
a premiere in fact what we
es un estreno de hecho lo que lo que
want is for the 27th I mean today is 26
queremos es que el 27 O sea ya hoy es 26
tomorrow it is already the premiere or rather it is
mañana esté esté ya el estreno o sea
scheduled Tomorrow is  Thursday No, well,
programado Mañana es jueves No pues el
Friday is already
viernes ya va a estar
scheduled, Cabrera comes out.
programado sale yao
Look, the truth is, I'm going to
Cabrera Mira la verdad eso sí os voy a
answer you, uh, at first I had a
contestar eh en un principio tenía un
uh I had a scene planned in which
eh tenía una escena planeada en la que
several people were seen entering bars,
se veían a varios entrando entre rejas
no, but [ __ ], it's that there have been several
no pero [__] es que han sido varios
this
este
year, but the truth is that since
año pero la verdad es que como colabora
so many people collaborate, well, mm I've become a little
tanta gente pues mm me he puesto un poco
whiter, okay, so you
más blanquito vale para que me
understand, but it's not like it's
entendáis pero es que tampoco es como
super relevant, uh, of
super relevante eso eh
course. I wanted it to be zero to
claro Es que quería que fuera cero
reprimand anyone, zero to reprimand
increpar a nadie cero increpar a
anyone, the Twitter community comes out,
nadie sale la comunidad de
well, let's see,
Twitter bueno a ver salen salen
tiktokers come out, some telesalseo comes out. Yeah,
tiktokers sale algo de telesalseo Sí
man, of course, obviously
hombre claro eso sí evidentemente te
you've become lukewarm Javi Let's see, if it were only my video, if it were mine. Yes, yes, if I go out there hitting, you know, but of course, if more people already collaborate, who don't want to get involved in anything, well, I do
que no quieren verse involucrado en nada
n't want them to be uncomfortable or to
pues no quiero que se incomoden o que se
regret it,
arrepientan
not the geeks,
no los friky no
Aaron Mercury doesn't come out, no way, no
s sale Aaron Mercury ni de coña ni de
[ __ ]
[__]
way. But hey, we have to remember it
coña Pero bueno tenemos que recordarlo
today for when we close the live show, okay, we
hoy para cuando cerremos el directo vale
have to remember it  again okay
tenemos que recordarlo otra vez vale Ya
For now there are 15 people here who
de momento aquí hay 15 personas que
know that you have to be there on the 28th at
sabéis que tenéis que estar el 28 a las
8 eh Don't let me down eh I didn't let me down dude don't do it,
8 eh No me fallis eh no me fallé tío no
sel doesn't
hagáis sale sel ni de [__] coña
even come out nobody comes out dude
tampoco no sale nadie tío no sale
nobody comes out listen to me eh 28 at 8 okay 28 at
nadie escúchame eh 28 a las 8 vale 28 a
8 Likewise in every video that I upload
las 8 Igualmente en cada vídeo que suba
because today I recorded two videos for the
porque hoy he grabado dos vídeos para el
main one that I don't know if they'll come out before I
principal que no sé si saldrán antes lo
remember at the beginning okay Hey, I'm going to
recuerdo al principio vale Oye el voy
be a little heavy you
ser un poco pesado ya
know I'm going to be a little heavy eh
sabéis voy a ser un poquito pesado eh
I hope the hype is worth it Yeah the
Espero que el hype lo merezca Sí la
truth is that yes I would love to I have
verdad es que sí me encantaría tengo
a lot of attention I have the folder here with
mucha mira tengo aquí la carpeta con
all the brutes and I would love to
todos los brutos y me encantaría
show you something but it's that I don't
enseñaros algo pero es que es que no
want to give a spoiler let's see I'm going to look to
quiero hacer spoiler a ver voy a mirar a
see if I can put something wait but
ver si puedo poneros algo espera pero
just so you can see a little bit of the quality
solo para que veáis un poco la calidad
eh I mean no I'm not going to spoil it's that the
eh o sea no no voy a spoilear es que lo
best thing is that you find it as a
suyo es que os lo encontréis de de
surprise
sorpresa
but the thing is that I'm really anxious
pero lo que pasa que tengo mucha ansia
dude but at least so that people
tío pero por lo menos para que la gente
don't think it's from  [ __ ] joke no, there are a
no se piense que es de [__] broma no es
lot of people who think it's a
que hay mucha gente que se cree que es
joke because of April Fool's Day
broma por el tema del día de los
man, let's see, magic dust to
tío a ver espera polvitos mágicos para
wish the best to the W project sparks
desearle lo mejor al proyecto W chispas
sparks I don't know why it seems to me that we are
chispas no sé porque me suena que te
going to funa you not being able to streamers of l
vamos a funar no poder streamers de l
but with love and fiz Christmas grandpa I hope
pero con cariño y fiz Navidad abuelo es
you had a good time and thanks
que te la hayas pasado bien y gracias
for the gift of appearing if there are people
por el regalo de aparecer si hay gente
from latan yes there are people from latan Of course there are
de latan si hay gente de latan Claro que
people from latan how could there not be people
hay gente de latan cómo no va a ha gente
from
de
latan
latan
look look I'm just going to put this but
mira mira solo os voy a poner esto pero
so that you can see that it's not a joke okay
para que veáis que no es una broma vale
so that you can see a little bit of the quality okay I
para que veáis un poco la calidad vale o
mean I'm just going to put this which is
sea solamente os voy a poner esto que es
one click and that's it Okay, I mean they are
un click y ya está Vale o sea son tomas
outtakes in fact Of course
falsas de hecho
streamers from latan and
Claro que salen streamers de latan y
tiktoker and people appear, of course some have
tiktoker y gente claro algunos han
collaborated and others appear in
colaborado y otros pues salen en en
scenes it's a beastly
escenas va bestial
cinema
cine
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Look okay I mean it's cinema eh I mean it's
Mira vale o sea es cine eh o sea es
absolutely cinema
absolutamente cine
eh It's just so you can see the quality and
eh Es solo para que veáis la calidad y
so that you can see that it's not a joke
para que veáis que no es broma
okay let's see but those are my scenes
vale a ver pero esas son mis escenas
Of course but  no no no no but but let's
Claro pero no no no no pero pero s vamos
set a goal what goal do we set
a poner un objetivo qué objetivo ponemos
kids
chavalería
50 50 of the blues in 3
50 50 de los azules en 3
hours and I'm going to put finance the
horas y voy a poner financiar el
rewind to see if I can recover a little bit
rewind a ver si recupero un poquillo
no I don't know how much I've invested the
no no sé cuánto habré invertido la
truth is in doing this Well I don't know in
verdad en hacer esto Pues tampoco sé
the end either The salaries of the Editors and
finalmente Los sueldos de los Editores y
others I don't really know how much I've
demás no sé realmente cuánto he
invested let's see I've traveled I've had to
invertido a ver He viajado he tenido que
rent
alquilar
things but I don't know I don't know the truth I don't think that
cosas pero no sé no sé la verdad no creo
much you don't pay them Javi
mucho no les pagues Javi
Well I've had to hire
Bueno he tenido que contratar
hitmen what what what impression did the
sicarios qué qué qué impresión os ha
first one give you is it is that scene that
dado la primera es es esa escena esa
false take that I showed you what
toma falsa que os he enseñado qué
impression did it
impresión os ha
give you in cinema cinema
dado n cine cine
cinema it will be called rwi hispano No man it will be
cine se llamará rwi hispano No hombre se
called rwi
llamará rwi
202 24 there it is a kiss
202 24 ya está un beso
tesa What's up tesa How are we How did it
tesa Qué pasa tesa Cómo estamos Cómo ha
go today tesa are they going to put a ban on you for
ido hoy tesa te van a poner un Ban por
putting up such hot content grandpa
poner un contenido tan caliente abuelo
I came back horny face I came back
me vine carita calenturienta ya me vine
and I'm leaving a
y ya me voy un
kiss it seems like a movie no no no no we have
beso parece película no no no no se ha
done the best we can grandpa let
hecho lo mejor que podemos abuelito
's  spam the sick so he
vamos a spamear a lo enfermo para que
gets a lot of visits
tenga muchas visitas corazón
red heart yes yes yes man you have to That
rojo sí sí sí hombre tenéis que Eso ya
depends on you
depende de ustedes
how ugly the thumbnail me the thumbnail I don't
qué fea la miniatura me la miniatura no
know if it's going to be final eh Because
sé si va a ser definitiva eh Porque
because there are people who were not satisfied
porque hay gente que no quedó conforme
with the
con la
thumbnail And then a Tommy eh He told me
miniatura Y entonces un Tommy eh Me dijo
that Tommy not the one from the chat
que Tommy el de no el de la tertulia
but the other Tommy told me he recommended
sino el otro Tommy me dijo me recomendó
a kid for us to do
a un chaval para que hiciéramos
but of course the thing is that I don't
pero es que claro que lao es que yo no
want it to be a humiliating thumbnail
quiero que sea una miniatura humillante
or anything like that you know it can't be like that
ni nada de eso sabes sea no puede
Tommy's thumbnails
serlo las miniaturas de Tommy algunas
sometimes are
veces lo son
not that it looks more like a movie but you see
no que parezca más de una peli pero veis
the
mal la
thumbnail wrong we could put a thumbnail
miniatura podríamos poner una miniatura
of pipepino
de pipepino
and you go saying take it [ __ ] old man while
y vais diciendo toma [__] viejo mientras
not titling it is a sandwich all good we will
que no lo titul es bocadillo todo bien
be at the
estaremos en el
premiere face throwing a kiss bouquet of
estreno cara lanzando un beso ramo de
flowers and besides if you can
flores y aparte si podéis
if you want to save now
si queréis ahorraros ahora
the superchat members and
los miembro superchat y esas
stuff wait for me my wife that if I
cosas espérate me p mi mujer que si me
throw a c butt that I
ech un c colilla que se me ha
forgot if you want eh if you can
olvidado si queréis eh si podéis
save now The Super chat the
ahorraros ahora Los Super chat los
members and stuff just in case  do you want to
miembros y esas cosas por si lo queréis
leave it for Saturday
dejar para el sábado
eh It would also be good because the Because the one
eh También estaría bien porque la Porque
that is seen in the in the premiere like
la que se vea en el en el estreno como
a lot of movement you know like a lot of
mucho movimiento sabes como mucho
movement of Super chat message member
movimiento de Super chat mensaje miembro
and such so that it looks like the
y tal para que se vea como el extreno
apotheotic premiere that I imagine that will
apoteósico que yo me imagino que eso
position the AI ​​​​is so noticeable that it
posicionará se nota tanto la ia que
looks tacky But what
queda cutre Pero qué
ia but really is that
ía pero de verdad es que eso me lo puso
someone put that to me on Twitter someone put that to me it's
un me lo puso alguien en Twitter me puso
not that it's that it's that IB is
alguien no es que es que es que IB está
made with Look Sorry sorry I
hecho cona Mira Perdona perdona lo
tried we tried to make it so that it would
intenté intentamos que iba se
turn into Hulk but by pressing
convirtiera en Hulk pero apretando
pressing he almost shits himself and we had to
apretando casi se caga encima y tuvimos
do it with ia host the balls of
que hacerlo con ía [__] los [__] de
the people Eh but how do you know I don't see it
la gente Eh pero cómo sabes yo no la veo
bad to me it seems to me it seems very
mal a mí me me parece a mí me parece muy
pretty striking the miniature face
guapa impactante la miniatura cara
smiling with heart eyes a kiss
sonriendo con ojos de corazón un beso
tesa no no the people saying oh it's that you can
tesa no no la peña diciendo ay es que se
see that ivai is made with ia he is
nota que ivai está hecho con ía está
turning into
convirtiéndose en
Hulk he is turning into Hulk he did
Hulk está convirtiéndose en Hulk
not really turn into hul I will be
no se convirtió en hul de verdad estaré
traveling in Córdoba but I will not miss it
de viaje en Córdoba pero no me lo
tecu Fran's is not G  Man Fran is
tecu el de Fran no es G hombre Fran está
obviously retouched of course he is
retocado evidentemente claro que está
retouched he has not become Goku the
retocado no se ha convertido en Goku la
mother who gave birth to you go [ __ ]
madre que os parió iros a tomar por
yourselves the mother who gave birth to you eh the ones in the
culo la madre que os parió eh los de la
thumbnail appear in the video man well
miniatura salen en el vídeo hombre pues
why do you think they are in the
ustedes por qué creéis que están en la
thumbnail man if you believe that if you believe
miniatura hombre si creéis que si creéis
that Fran is not in the
que Fran no sale en el
video what balls you have eh what balls
vídeo qué huevos tenéis eh qué huevos
you have beautiful
tenéis bonita
something interesting happened with Fran this year
pasó algo interesante con Fran este año
nothing
nada
nothing that they appear in the video does not
nada que salgan en el vídeo no quieren
mean that they have recorded a scene for me
decir que me hayan grabado una escena
eh that they appear in the video they can appear
eh que salgan en el vídeo pueden salir
because they are there is some clip of them no
porque están sale algún clip de ellos no
or something about them of course Ari
o alguna cosa de ellos per claro Ari ha
had a breakup this year no Auron
tenido una ruptura este año no auron
Auron has had two breakups this
auron ha tenido dos rupturas este
year So anyone can say Sao well
año Así cualquiera dice Sao bueno
you see the video and that's it
ustedes lo veis el vídeo y ya está
Auron there is still time for a
auron todavía está a tiempo de una
third it's true it's true Luare there is
tercera es verdad es verdad luare
still time for a third
todavía está a tiempo de una tercera
Well let's see things not what we see
Bueno vamos a ver cosas no qué vemos
first places we see what with n it
primero lugares vemos lo de lo de n me
seemed
ha parecido a mí
spectacular to me to me what with nimus it
espectacular a mí lo de nimus me ha
seemed like something you say dude What are you
parecido una cosa que dices tú tío Qué
doing but s super cold also eh super
haces pero s super fría además eh super
free  also super free good night you can
free además super gratuito buenas noches
imagine Well I can
imagínate Pues yo a ustede
imagine delox using the nimu account
imagínate delox usando la cuenta de nimu
man I think so actually no I don't
hombre Yo creo que sí la verdad no no lo
know but I understand that
sé pero yo entiendo que
yes I understand that yes Well the thing
sí Yo entiendo que sí Bueno la cosa
starts Yesterday when I was leaving
comienza Ayer cuando yo me estaba yendo
my wife's grandmother's house
de casa de la abuela de mi
and I come across a tweet from
mujer y me encuentro con con un tweet de
nimu The tweet was this one uh the tweet was
nimu El tet era este eh el tet era
responding to one of the clips dude I mean I
respondiendo a a uno de los clip tío o
wasn't even messing with her
sea yo no estaba ni metiéndome con ella
or delos or anything uh I mean look at you
ni con delos ni nada eh o sea fíjate tú
I'm so busy with the rewind thing
que estoy tan liado con lo del rewind
that well luar she's passing me some
que bueno luar me va pasando alguna
news and we're tweeting something in fact I
noticia y vamos teteando algo de hecho
think I have tweets around here eh that I haven't
creo que tengo por ahí tweet eh que no
tweeted news that I haven't tweeted
he twite noticias que no he tiado
yet because I'm with what I'm
todavía porque estoy con lo estoy
really focused on that it's already the
centrad simo en eso que son ya los
last the last hours part to
últimos las últimas horas parte para
finish it and the and the thing is that I
terminarlo y la y la movida es que me
come across this tweet but apart It's that
encuentro con este tweet pero aparte Es
almost just as I picked up the phone
que casi que justo cogía el teléfono
when she had posted the tweet I
cuando cuando ella había puesto el tweet
was getting in the in the taxi
era montándome en el en el taxi de
back you know it was a  clip dude it was a clip
vuelta sabes era un clip tío era un clip
in which she was with delox Okay
en el que ella estaba con con delox Vale
and delo was a live of hers from the
y delo era un directo de ella de estos
last few days that she's already doing
últimos días que ya está haciendo
live with her face and all and delox comes
directo con su cara y eso y entra delox
into the room takes off the microphone and
en la habitación la quita el micrófono y
starts with his Dallas spiel I don't know
se pone con su retahila de Dallas no sé
what without saying Dallas's name But
qué sin decir el nombre de Dallas Pero
well obviously referring to
bueno evidentemente refiriéndose a
Dallas
Dallas
okay And I simply in the tweet what I
vale Y yo simplemente en el twit lo que
put was something like well there you
puse era algo así como bueno por ahí lo
have it now we're going to see it no but it was
tenéis ahora lo vamos a ver no pero era
like eh nimu And delos talk about
así como eh nimu Y delos hablan de
Dallas in a live and they're against
Dallas en un directo y están en contra
the bully I don't know what something like that okay
del bully no sé qué alguna cosa así vale
eh or delos talks about his specialty
eh o delos habla de su especialidad la
delox's specialty is not cryptocurrencies
delox no es las criptomonedas
if it were delox delox was promoting crp
si fuera delox delox promocionaba crp
Pain was promoting
Pain promocionaba a
nimbus well And he said that bitcoin was going
nimbus bueno Y decía que el bitcoin iba
to fall to zero then
a caer a cero entonces la especialidad
delox's specialty what he studies the most is Dallas he gets
de delox lo que él más estudia es Dallas
up and goes to bed thinking about
é se levanta y se acuesta pensando en
Dallas OK Well the specialty thing
Dallas OK Bueno ya lo de especialidad
is also very much in quotes because of the
también queda muy entre comillas por el
fact that he doesn't give one yesterday or the day
tema de que de que no da una ayer o
before yesterday for example he was
antes de ayer por ejemplo se estaba
inventing a kiss Lucho yesterday  or the day before
inventando un beso Lucho ayer o antes de
yesterday he was inventing that he
ayer se estaba inventando que él se
had met with the seo of bitmark to
había reunido con el seo de bitmark para
delist pambi and it turns out that the
deslistar pambi y ya resulta que el
Dallas that we will see now has been
Dallas que ahora lo veremos ha estado
commenting that no, it is that pambi the
comentando que no que es que pambi la
first has been delisted But why does it
primera lo han deslistado Pero por qué
not have
no tiene
liquidity Claro is inactive without
liquidez Claro está inactiva sin
liquidity they have delisted it like
liquidez lo han deslistado al igual que
many other tokens Well then delos
otros muchos tokens Bueno pues el delos
says that they have delisted it because he has
dice que lo han deslistado porque él se
met with the seo but with which seo are
ha reunido con el seo pero con qué seo
you going to meet with delox
te vas a reunir tú delox
take invent Well then like everything but he does
toma invent Bueno pues como todo per que
n't get tired my love I'm dying to see the
no se cansa mi amor Me muero por ver el
rewind it gives me more excitement than the
rewind me da más ilusión que el año
new year I send you a big kiss on the mouth with
nuevo te mando un besote en la boca con
all due respect to Lorena With all due
todo respeto para Lorena yo Con todo el
respect I give it to you I hope I hope it doesn't
respeto te lo doy Ojalá ojalá que no os
disappoint you I hope it doesn't despair you and and
desilusione ojalá que no os desion y y
fill you up I think it's going to leave you with your
os llene yo creo que os va a dejar con
ass broken I think it's going to leave you with your
el culo roto yo creo que os va a dejar
ass broken eh Maybe it's me who
el culo roto eh A lo mejor soy yo que
is very excited about the
estoy muy emocionado con el
video talking to the seo he says  gachon
vídeo hablando con el seo dice el gachon
speaks Now about why you removed your entire
habla Ya de por qué has quitado todo tu
channel delox that you removed the
canal delox que has quitado el canal
entire channel and you said it was because you didn't
entero y has dicho que era porque no te
like the thumbnails police stations that
gustaban las miniaturas comisarías que
close at 3 Well trust yourself trust yourself the
cierran a las 3 Bueno fíate tú fíate tú
things that these
la de cosas que se han inventado esta
people have invented in the year that are a picture that
gente en el año que son un cuadro que
are a [ __ ] picture that we don't comment on even
son un [__] cuadro que no comentamos ni
half of the things they do is
la mitad de las cosas que hacen
worth the complaint from Ricky Eddie to Dallas
vale la denuncia de Ricky Eddie a Dallas
that didn't exist finally the
que no existió finalmente la demanda
class action lawsuit by pambi to Dallas that doesn't exist either that
colectiva por pambi a Dallas que tampoco
Dallas couldn't step foot in Andorra
la hay que Dallas no podía pisar andorra
because he had an Alami order it was a
porque tenía una orden de alami era
lie that the police stations closed at
mentira que las comisarías cerraban a
3 in the afternoon what can I tell you what I
las 3 de la tarde qué te digo qué Te
tell you about Christopher Pain no what's going on with
digo de christop pain no qué pasa con
Christopher Pain I mean and and they come to
christop Pain o sea y y te vienen a
clarify and they bring you my
aclarar y te vienen mi contrato de
confidentiality agreement if you knew how many
confidencialidad si supieras cuántas
hours I've listened to you and everything that you've
horas te he escuchado y todo lo que me
helped me without knowing it your mother must
has ayudado sin saberlo tu madre debe de
be very proud thanks for all
estar muy orgullosa gracias por todos
these years What a nice guy a kiss a
estos años Qué bonito tío un beso un
kiss Thank you very much
beso Muchas gracias
man the [ __ ] [ __ ] that they've
tío la de [__] [__] que se han
invented no that was invented this
inventado no que se ha inventado esta
very week  that I had spoken with him
misma semana que había hablado con el
with the bmark seo man they are
con el seo de bmark tío que son
ridiculous and he comes and comes to
ridículos y me viene y me viene a
clarify if he is talking about Dallas or not
aclarar si está hablando de Dallas o no
in that clip, I mean, look at you if they
en ese clip o sea fíjate tú si tienen
still have things to clarify and he comes to
cosas por aclarar todavía y me viene a
clarify this for me, okay, well about his Face
aclarar Esto vale Bueno sobre su Face
reveal what I have done It has been
reveal lo que he hecho yo Ha sido
tweeting as news we have not gotten into
twitear como noticia no nos hemos metido
her here or her physique as
aquí con ella ni con su físico como está
Twitter is doing everything we commented on nothing the
haciendo todo Twitter nada comentamos el
other day we reacted to the part where he
otro día reaccionamos a la parte que
did a Face reveal and in the title he put
hizo un Face reveal y en el título puso
Dallas man how are you guys with
a Dallas tío que por huevos estáis con
Dallas man you have assumed that
Dallas tío que tenéis asumido que
your attention eh what Okay what's up
vuestra atención eh qué Va lne qué va
daughter what's up
hija qué
But I hope so what's up But I hope so
va Pero espero que sí qué va Pero espero
and if not then we have this
que sí y si no pues tenemos esto
alne we already have this eh
alne esto ya lo tenemos eh
What did the Face reveal do the Face reveal did it
Qué hizo el Face reveal el Face reveal
with the title of Dallas well man
lo hizo con con el título de Dallas tío
at no time did I mention it
total en ningún momento lo menciono en
directly in the clip so the ones
el clip directamente así que los
in session are you Ah okay I mean okay
sesionados sos vos Ah vale o sea vale
you are talking about Dallas in your
que tú estás hablando de Dallas en tu
clip in your live your boyfriend who takes
clip en tu directo tu novio que te quita
the microphone from you let's go that I think this
el micrófono vamos que yo creo que este
tweet Of course because in the tweet I am
tweet Claro porque yo en el tweet estoy
talking about
hablando de
delox not from her it's in her live
delox no de ella es en el directo de
but the one I say delox
ella pero el que el que digo delo
takes advantage of it, I mean now we're going to see the
aprovecha que o sea ahora vamos a ver el
TT okay but I'm talking about delox
TT vale pero yo estoy hablando de delox
this is written by delox from his
esto lo escribe delox desde la cuenta de
relative's account Also I'm telling you
la parienta Además ya te digo yo a ti
that this guy is paying Bot on Twitter
que este tío está pagando Bot en Twitter
at this moment because just like they had I don't
aá momento porque al igual que tenían no
know how many thousands of likes every time he
sé cuántos miles de likes cada vez que
posted a tweet about the 10 bullets he had
ponía un tweet de las 10 balas que tenía
against Dallas the fake reveal of nimu has
contra Dallas el fake reveal de nimu ha
had 100,000 likes on Twitter I
tenido 100000 likes en Twitter yo
personally don't believe that this girl has that
personalmente No me creo que esta tía
support
tenga ese apoyo
you go on Twitter and search for
tú te metes en Twitter y buscas sobre
nimo and that she has 100,000 likes But you
nimo y que tenga 100.000 likes Pero tú
know what 100,000 likes are on a tweet
sabes lo que son 100000 likes en un twit
if my account which is the most viral for
si mi cuenta que es la más viral de
gossip when a tweet goes viral for it to
salseo cuando se viraliza un tweet para
have 30,000 likes a very very
que tenga 30.000 likes un tweet muy muy
very viral tweet with millions of views I mean it does
muy viral de millones de visitas O sea
n't make sense 100,000 likes on
no tiene sentido 100.000 likes el tweet
her tweet announcing her Face
de ella anunciando su Face
review I don't believe it and and and  coming from
review no me lo creo y y y viniendo de
something related to delox well
algo relacionado con delox pues
obviously not not
evidentemente no no
giving well total trust yourself what you come
dando bueno total fíate tú lo que viene
to tell me implying that I am
a decirme dando a entender que estoy
referring to him leaves you very two or
haciendo alusión a él te deja muy dos o
rather as if it were a different point or
sea como si fuera otro punto diferente o
rather the three points talk about the same thing and he
sea los tres puntos hablan de lo mismo y
tells you one two and three two
te dice un dos y tres dos dando a
implying that I am making reference to him
entender que estoy haciendo alusión a él
leaves you in a very bad position doggy why do you have to
te deja muy mal parado perrito por qué
talk to me about
me tienes que hablar de
doggy What obsession do you have with
perrito Qué obsesión tienes con los
doggies nimu I mean I am
perritos nimu o sea yo yo te estoy
insulting you I have disrespected you in
insultando te he faltado el respeto en
that tweet You don't know how to talk to
ese tweet No sabes hablar con las
people because then when they humiliate you
personas porque luego cuando te humillan
cry of course then the cries come those of
lloras claro luego vienen los los lloros
you and your
los tal tuyos y de tu
boyfriend why I mean what did the TT have for
novio por qué O sea qué tenía el TT para
you to insult me ​​and call me doggy
que tú me insultes y me llames perrito
per lo que era I do know why you
per claro Bueno yo sí sé para queé me
call me doggy so that they applaud you the
llamas perrito para que te aplaudan los
only harassers who follow your roll
únicos acosadores que os siguen el rollo
harassers who may be
acosadores que a lo mejor tienen algunos
9 years old man then you go into the
9 años tío luego te metes en los
profiles and they are creatures I mean it can't
perfiles y son criaturas O sea no puede
be any other way adults people
ser de otra manera personas adultas
with two in front or
personas con dos de frente o chavales
more kids  or less mature no no you are not going to
más o menos maduros no no te no te van a
get Las Palmas because you say puppy or
tocar Las Palmas porque digas perrito o
kennel. Hello Javi, what are you doing here today? Well
perreira Hola Javi Qué haces aquí hoy
look K, Christmas is for
Pues mira K pues la Navidad son para
getting together with family and I'm here with my
reunirse en familia y estoy aquí con mi
family with
familia con
you three, you forgot to mention the
ustedes tres te olvidaste de citar la
part where I say that
parte en la que digo que el bullying
massive bullying Should be the closure of the channel Or do you
masivo Debería ser de cierre del canal O
support massive bullying, man, well I
apoyas el bullying masivo hombre pues yo
don't support massive bullying nimu But
no apoyo el bullying masivo nimu Pero a
I haven't forgotten to mention any
mí no se me ha olvidado citar ninguna
part, it's a headline, there they have the click,
parte es un titular ahí tienen el click
people and they are going to see it in the headline
la gente y lo van a ver tú en el titular
so that they take up less than 200 or 160
para que ocupen menos de los 200 o 160
characters, I don't remember how many there are,
caracteres no me acuerdo Cuántos son
but I like the headline to be seen,
pero a mí me gusta que se vea el titular
what draws attention if you say it
lo que llame la atención si tú lo dices
in the clip. Well, very well Alex, a kiss,
en el clip Pues muy bien Alex un beso
but it doesn't make sense
pero es que no tiene sentido
and now he
y ahora
says crappy
dice viejito
old man, you see this, a normal TT
pedorro ustedes veis esto un TT normal
to address a person Wait, I
para dirigirse a una persona Espérate
have to, they just sent me a
que tengo que que me acaban de mandar un
clip that I was waiting for a moment,
cli que estaba esperando un momento
silence, eh
silencio eh
silence,
silencio
al al al al buah
al
what a barbarity,
buah vaya barbaridad
man, a kiss Alex  what a
tío un beso Alex
barbarity d what a
vaya barbaridad
barbarity When you see this
barbaridad Cuando veáis esto
eh When you see this man well we're almost
eh Cuando veáis esto tío pues ya poco
closed
más ya cerramos
eh Hi grandpa Merry Christmas I hope you had a
eh Hola abuelo Feliz Navidad Espero la
good here we are
hayas pasado bien aquí andamos con las
eager to see your rewind I just wanted to
ansias de ver tu rewind solo quería
ask people will show up from both
preguntar aparecerá gente tanto de
Spain and the tam There's no problem if you don't
España como de la tam No hay líos si no
want to answer No no yes man they
quieres responder No no sí s hombre
seem like take grandpa as a thank you
parecen toma abuelo en agradecimiento
for working on a holiday by the way Take off the
por currar en festivo de paso Quítate la
and lamentable delox I say nimu a kiss a
y lamentable delox digo nimu un beso un
kiss
beso
[Music]
[Música]
eh Let's see I would love to put the audio
eh A ver Me encantaría poneros el audio
of the click that they sent me I would
del click que me han mandado Me
love to put the
encantaría poneros el
audio but for the audio we would have to
audio pero para el audio tendríamos que
reach 50 super chat at least
llegar a los 50 super chat por lo menos
a
un
kiss no no the video no the video no the video you
beso no no el vídeo no el vídeo no el
see it in the premiere no no but
vídeo lo veis en el extreno no no pero
the video is that you are going to love it man
el vídeo es que os va a encantar tío
[ __ ] What talent is here eh to Mario
hostias Qué talento hay aquí eh a Mario
a
un
kiss what talent what talent the people
beso qué talento qué talento la gente
man also The thing is that
tío además Es que lo que pasa es que la
when people have been sending it they have been bringing
gente cuando ha ido mandándolo ha ido
out the
sacándola la
truth people when they have been doing
verdad la gente cuando ha ido haciendo
each one doing their scene They have brought it
cada uno haciendo su escena Se la han
out Maribel  How are you? I ca
sacado Maribel Cómo estás
n't wait for the 28th. Nothing. Me
no puedo esperar para el 28 nada Yo
neither, man. I'll see it finished
tampoco hombre yo lo veré terminado ya
tomorrow night. I think
mañana por la noche Yo creo que ya
tomorrow night or yes, I think
mañana por la noche o sí yo creo que ya
tomorrow night I'll see the
mañana por la noche veré yo la versión
final version. But if we reach those 50
final pero si llegamos a esos 50
Super
objetivos de Super
chat goals, I'll put the audio on for you and let's go. When I
chat os pongo el audio y vamos ya cuando
put this audio on, you're 100% going to stop bothering me that it's
os ponga este audio ya 100% me vais a
trolling. When you listen to this audio, you're
troleo cuando escuchéis este audio ya al
100% going to stop bothering me that
100% me vais a dejar de tocar los huevos
this is trolling.
con que esto es un troleo
Hey, the audio. I'll put a little bit of the
eh el audio os pongo un poquito del
audio. I'll put a little bit of the audio. If we
audio os pongo un poquito del audio si
reach
llegamos a los
50,
50 al objetivo
that goal. The audio is a scene. The audio is
ese el audio es una escena el audio es
the audio of a
el audio de una
scene. It's trolling, grandpa. It's not trolling,
escena es troleo abuelo no es troleo
damn. When you listen to this audio, you're going
[__] cuando escuchéis este audio ya Vais
to see that it's not trolling. It's just that, let's see. I already
a ver que no es troleo Es que a ver s ya
knew that he was going to say that because
ya sabía que iba a decir eso porque
man, it's the 28th, but no, damn,
hombre son es el día 28 pero que no [__]
it's that I would have liked it to
que es que a mí me hubiera gustado que
be the 26th, paimon. Quote, a kiss.
fuera el 26 paimon cito un beso
A lot.  thanks always for the support
Muchísimas gracias siempre por el apoyo
dude another 50 member paimon cito and another
tío otr 50 miembro paimon cito y otros
50 Mari you you you you you that I
50 Mari tú tú tú tú tú que que que os
calmed down that you calm down
calmé que os
Okay let's continue with the
calmis Bueno vamos a seguir con el
gossip And if we reach 50 super
chisme Y si llegamos a los 50 super
chats I'll put the audio only the
chats esos os pongo el audio solamente
audio
el audio eh solamente el audio para que
eh only the audio so you can see so you can get more hype God How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful How beautiful Look I just sent alne It's that I don't know if alne is here I don't
la veo en el chat me está hablando aaris
see her in the chat she's talking to me aaris another 50 come on man come on man What a machine eh Let's see questions that come to me more or less how long it will last and are you going to put restrictions so that people don't react Or don't poke it live like or rather I ask about
en directo como o más bien pregunto por
it Pacman And by the way, check the
él Pacman Y por cierto revisa la
Twitter community benedita
comunidad de Twitter benedita
remind me before closing because no no no no no
recuérdamelo antes de cerrar por que no
[ __ ] way let
que no que no ni de [__] coña que cada
everyone see it when they want Let's see it
uno lo vea cuando le dé la gana A ver
would be a detail it would be a detail that
sería un detalle sería un detalle que
while it is the
mientras que es el
premiere no but  I'm not going to ban it if
estreno no pero no lo voy a prohibir si
it happens if someone catches you live at
lo si le Pilla a alguien en directo en
that moment and wants to see it, I don't care,
ese momento lo quiere ver me da igual
man. I would prefer the ideal would be that they did
hombre Yo preferiría lo ideal sería que
n't send everyone to be at
que no que mandaran a todo el mundo a
the premiere, imagine if it
que estén en el extreno imaginaros que
were a premiere of I don't know 4000
sea un extreno de yo que sé 4000
people 5000 people no or the more the
personas 5000 personas no o cuantos más
better but but if they want to
mejor pero pero si los quieren
react at the same
reaccionar en el mismo
time the video is for everyone I
momento es para todo el mundo el vídeo O
mean it seems
sea que a mí me parece
perfect to me no no no no and that you
perfecto que no que no que no y que
upload a lot of clicks to Twitter and
subáis muchos clicks a Twitter y a todas
everywhere the ideal would be to move it
partes lo ideal sería eso que lo moviera
there man promoting itself
ahí hombre promocionándose
in fact I would like
de hecho me gustaría que lo reaccionara
as many people as possible to react to it to see the
cuanta más gente mejor para ver las
faces like the reactions No if you like it or
caras en plan las reacciones No si gusta
not
no
like it, ra has won a
gusta le ha tocado a ra una
membership if it goes It
membresía si va Lo
promotes it I'll tell you but I don't think so no I don't think one
promociona ya te digo yo pero no creo no
of the big ones I don't think
creo de los grandes No creo yo que lo
anyone will see it no I don't think so let's see there are scenes
vea nadie no no creo a ver hay escenas
to
que
see and they will see it but man,
ver y lo verán pero hombre ya
promoting it is that let's see things
promocionarlo es que a ver las cosas
as they are being a channel like
como son al ser un canal como el
mine there are times when there are things that put you
mío hay veces que hay cosas que echan
off not seeing related or things
para atrás no verse relacionado o cosas
like that but
así pero bueno
Well it's difficult and gossip of course there are gossip things So you know what happens yes it's true that they might put scenes and then the gossip ones go by I don't know come on there's nothing wrong with it eh to see it eh
tiene nada de malo eh para verlo eh en
live eh There's nothing wrong with it it
un directo eh No tiene nada de malo
has tributes to beautiful things
tiene homenajes a las cosas bonitas
too and
también y
so on well This is what we were
demás bueno Esto que nos habíamos
left with with this
quedado con esto
pathetic well Total that the move It's that
patético bueno Total que la movida Es
I answered this
que yo le contesté a este
tweet with too much respect for what it
twet con demasiado respeto para el que
deserves for my taste I don't know what you guys
merece para mi gusto No sé ustedes qu os
think let's come to I mean
parece vamos vienes a o sea todo el
everyone sees my Twitter the other day Carola
mundo ve mi Twitter el otro día Carola
for example also responded to a tweet
por ejemplo respondió también a un tweet
because she wanted to give more context to a
porque quería darle más contexto a un
tweet that I had posted a news that
twet que yo había puesto una noticia que
I had
yo había
posted ar everyone comes and It's
puesto ar todo el mundo viene y
okay but but come Like that you see crappy old
No pasa nada pero pero venir Así vieo
man crappy old man
pedorro viejito pedorro
a kiss
un beso
Sander they are small children no but it's that
Sander son niños pequeños no pero es que
what way are they I mean yes yes
esto qué forma son de O sea si si
obviously if someone messes with you
evidentemente si alguien se mete contigo
you have the right to respond no
estás en el derecho de de responderle no
but this is that this is a disgrace
pero esto es que esto es una vergüenza
the truth  I mean, when does the
la verdad O sea en qué momento viene lo
first thing come with the thing that
primero con la de cosa que que tienen
these people have to clarify with the with the
que aclarar esta gente con la con las
things that these people have to clarify
cosas que tienen que aclarar esta gente
Alex a
Alex un
kiss come clarify this [ __ ] as
beso venir a aclarar esta chorrada como
if they weren't talking about Dallas and it's like but
si no hablaran de Dallas y es como pero
if you're talking to Dallas and about
si estáis hablando con el Dallas y del
Dallas all the
Dallas todo el
time if you have Dallas in your
tiempo si tenéis a Dallas en el
mind all the time what does it matter
pensamiento todo el tiempo qué más da
why do you come to clarify this [ __ ] and
Para qué vienes a aclarar esa gilipo y
then the puppy thing I don't know what demanding
luego lo de perrito No sé qué demandando
the type of public that they demand no what
al tipo de público que ellos demandan no
happened because I answered him
qué es lo que pasó porque yo le respondí
with respect whether you want it or not more than what they
con respeto quieras que no más de lo que
deserve no and
se merecen no
nimu is a headline if you can't avoid being
y nimu es un titular si no puedes evitar
disrespectful or talking about puppies you
faltar al respeto o hablar de perritos
shouldn't manage the networks
no deberías manejar las redes
you
tú lo
want it I want to feel your body next
quieres quiero sentir tu cuerpo juntito
to mine because my soul has no time
al mío porque mi alma no tiene tiempo
feeling
sintiendo
cold I want to feel your body
frío quiero sentir tu cuerpo
because
porque
frer I want to feel your body of mine because
frer quiero sentir tu cuerpo mío porque
my at time and t I
mi al ti tiempo y t
want to feel your body of mine because M
lo quiero sentir tu cuerpo mío porque M
time
tiempoo
frero
frero
tuero and no He just deleted the TT after a
tuero y no Solo lo ha eliminó el TT al
while people started
rato empezaron la gente a
putting quio
ponerle quio
body J to mine because my soul
cuerpo J al mío porque mi alma
has I want to feel your body because my
tiene quiero sentir tu cuerpo porque mi
Alo I want  feel your body of mine because
Alo quiero sentir tu cuerpo mío porque
my soul has no
mi alma no tiene
time I want to feel your body next to
tiempo quiero sentir tu cuerpo jun al
mine because my soul has no time if it's
mío porque mi alma no tiene tiempo si
cold if you want it
frío si lo quieres
forgive me that they're sending me that
perdonadme que me están mandando
what do you think do you think it was
eso qué creéis ustedes creéis que fue
her who wrote this or is it her boyfriend
ella la que escribió esto o es el novio
the boyfriend took her Twitter and then she
le cogió el Twitter el novio y y después
said to him go away delete delete that you
le dijo ella anda quita quita borra eso
're putting me in I don't know
que me estás metiendo a mí en no sé
what we already know that mood she's not she's not a
qué ya sabemos que nimo no es no es
good person the truth is she's not a good
buena persona la verdad no es buena
person
persona
well deleted deleted This okay I mean she deleted
bueno borró borró Esto vale o sea borró
the tweet say Ah well she
el tweet di Ah bueno pues se ha dado
realized the stupid thing she
cuenta de la pendejada que que ha
wrote because she's been
escrito porque ha venido faltando al
disrespecting and all that stuff Okay and
respeto y todo el rollo ese Vale
then she goes and I wake up this
y y luego va y me levanto esta
morning saying that she threw the
mañana con que me ha tirado el
video at me
vídeo
okay it was definitely her boyfriend then she deleted it the thing
vale fijo fue el novio luego lo borró
is that many times you give the
ella es que muchas veces des la
tite he many times there are things that are
tite él muchas veces hay cosas que son
his but I don't understand it I don't know if you
él pero no lo entiendo No sé si ustedes
see any
le veis alguna
logic the language is that of
lógica el lenguaje es el de
delox But what's the point of getting
delox Pero qué sentido tiene de meter a
your girlfriend into lawsuits
tu novia en pleitos
man what's the point of getting your girlfriend
tío qué sentido tiene meter a tu novia
into lawsuits
en pleitos
feel
sentir
body I just don't understand  what's the point of me
cuerpo es que no entiendo el qué sentido
messing with your girlfriend in platoo if I
tiene Met a tu novia en platoo si no me
'm not messing with you, I avoid messing with
estoy metiendo con yo esquivo meterme
nimu I always promise you eh And it
con con nimu Siempre os lo prometo eh Y
's not because of a lack of desire in some of the
no es por falta de de ganas en algunas
[ __ ] they do but I have a problem
cagadas que hacen pero yo tengo problema
with delox who is a slanderer okay
con delox que es un calumniador vale
apart from being a liar a fake and all the
aparte de un mentiroso un falso y todas
things that he is
las cosas que es
then messing with his girlfriend I see it
entonces meterme con la novia lo veo
as not the same eh as if they
como no es lo mismo eh que si se
messed with mine obviously it
metieran con la mía evidentemente
's not the same because mine doesn't, she doesn't even know
no es lo mismo porque la mía no no sabe
about this gossip I'm asking her right now
ni de esto salseo yo ahora mismo le
Who is nimo and she doesn't
pregunto mismo Quién es nimo y no lo
know okay
sabe vale
but but no I don't know I don't feel I don't
pero pero no no sé no me siento no me
feel comfortable but it won't be the same
siento cómodo me pero no será lo mismo
because it's that he's been
porque es que ya está todo el [__] día
messing with me all day long the content creator
metiose conmigo el creadora de contenido
but well I try to avoid it I try to avoid it
pero bueno intento
okay
esquivarlo intento esquivarlo vale
feeling cold If you
sintiendo frío Si tú lo
want it I want to feel your body mine
quieres quiero sentir tu cuerpo al mío
because my soul doesn't have time cold
porque mi alma no tiene tiempoo frío
loer I want to feel your body J mine
loer quiero sentir tu cuerpo J al mío
because my soul doesn't have time
porque mi alma no tiene tiempo
if I want to feel your body mine because my
si quiero sentir tu cuerpo mío porque mi
soul doesn't have time cold you
alma no tiene tiempoo frío tú
loer I want to feel your body jun
loer quiero sentir tu cuerpo jun
my
mi al ti
time I want to feel your
tiempoo quiero sentir tu
body says that passes the breaks live does
cuerpo dice que pasa las pausas en vivo
not forgive is that the girl is sending me
no perdona es que me está mandando la la
[Music]
[Música]
is sending me the clique well I'm not
me está mandando el clique bueno no os
going to put the clip but I put the
voy a poner el clip pero os pongo el
audio if we reach 50 super chat
audio si llegamos a los 50 super chat
that we already have 20 by the
que ya llevamos 20 por
way which t did they eliminate Javi well it is
cierto cuál t eliminaron Javi pues es
This look at it V delox takes advantage of the fact that nimu
Este míralo V delox aprovecha que nimu
was talking about the controversies on the
estaba hablando sobre las polémicas en
internet To contribute something about his
internet Para aportar algo sobre su
specialty Dallas be I'm talking
especialidad Dallas sea estoy hablando
about delox not
de delox no de
her okay she comes to answer
ella vale viene ella a contestar
saying why do you say that I have mentioned
diciendo por qué dices que he mencionado
Dallas but the thing is that well she
Dallas pero la movida es que bueno me
throws this tweet at me I appeal it Okay that's it
tira este tweet lo apelo dio Bueno ya
or rather I appeal this This is
está o sea lo apelo esto Esto se
obviously recovered
recupera evidentemente
and And I continue continuing with the with Christmas
e Y sigo continúo con la con la Navidad
I put this
pongo este
thread last night on Christmas Eve man it
hilo anoche en plena Nochebuena tío que
was Christmas Eve 3 in the morning that
fue Nochebuena las 3 de la mañana que
they live in Andorra
ellos viven en andorra
eh I don't know if the one of them will have gone to see
eh yo no sé si el de los habrá ido a ver
the
a la
family that would be logical no that
familia que sería lo lógico no que
surely last night they went to see the
seguramente anoche fueran a ver la
family I don't think they stayed  In
familia no creo que se quedaran en
Andorra last night on Christmas Eve Nimu
andorra anoche en plena Nochebuena nimu
came to insult me ​​for free when
vino a insultarme gratuitamente cuando
he realized that the result was not what he
comprobó que el resultado no fue el
expected he deleted the tweet and today I
esperado borró el tweet y hoy me
find that he is trying to suspend my
encuentro con que intenta suspender mi
Twitter account I don't know why you do fa
cuenta de Twitter no sé para qué haces
reveal when we saw your face a long time ago you
fa reveal si ya hace tiempo que te vimos
are a bad person you are
la cara eres mala persona
not a good person eh She is not a good
no es buena persona eh No es buena
person look at
persona fíjate
you who starts talking about Dallas of
tú que se pone a hablar de Dallas de
massive bullying when what she came to
masivo cuando ella lo que vino a
promote was this
promover era esto
Look back at the kennel you are Dallas's little dog make
Mira devuelta la perrera eres el perrito
your
Dallas dar pena a tu
mother feel sorry for you your mother seere your mother must
madre tu madre seere tu madre se debe
want to kill herself every day for having
querer matar todos los días por tener un
such a mentally ill son
hijo tan enfermo
exclaimed the little dog and Dallas is not
mental exclamó el perrito y Dallas no
disrespecting the public that they
respeto para el público que ellos
demand
demandan
okay one restraining order that does not
vale uno orden de alejamiento que no
exist two police stations that close at
existe dos comisarías que cierran a las
TR three class action lawsuit that does not exist
TR tres demanda colectiva que no existe
quattro hitmen disguised as r hostia
cuat sicarios disfrazados de r [__]
this is true hitmen No I already
esto es verdad sicarios No ya se me
forgot about Delox's hitmen no
olvidaban los sicarios de delox no que
by the way Delox said that he was going to
por cierto delox dijo que iba a
report the hitmen too do you
denunciar también lo de los sicarios
remember five the death of Serene another
acordáis cinco la muerte de serene otra
joke of these people six channel
payasada de esta gente seis canal
deleted by the thumbnails because he didn't
borrado por las miniaturas porque ya no
like the thumbnails anymore seven the
le gustaban las miniaturas siete las las
collaborations with crist Pain that by the
colaboraciones con crist Pain que por
way I forgot to tell you some
cierto se me olvidó comentaros algunas
things Ah already the delos At that moment he
cosas Ah ya el delos En aquel momento me
let go of my arm when I made the third
soltó el brazo cuando le hice el tercer
video on the main one and dig Ah come on I'll
vídeo en el principal y dig Ah venga lo
leave it here but I have more these days I'll make
dejo aquí pero tengo más estos días haré
a video eh surely main thing happens
un vídeo eh seguramente principal pasa
that I wouldn't like to mix it now with
que no me gustaría mezclarlo ahora con
the r Not even that [ __ ] dude these
el r Ni esa [__] tío de esta
people Chan manipulated dude So
gente lo Chan manipulado tío O sea que
the guy started editing and deleting the
se puso el tío a editar y a borrar las
discord conversations with
conversaciones de discord con
Dallas to then publish them as if they
Dallas para luego publicarlas como si
were something
fueran algo
You know, go on, you didn't have things to
Sabes anda que no teníais cosas que
clarify before if the cli before if
matizar antes de si el cli antes de si
in the cli I referred to you about dala or Rubio or
en el cli os referí a dala o al Rubio o
talking about puppies
hablar de perritos
Oh and listen to what they put in the what they
Ah y escúchame lo que han puesto en la
put in the report eh the
lo que ha puesto en el reporte eh el
paimon cito Thank you very much dude
paimon cito Muchísimas gracias tío
we've had 24 super chat eh we're
llevamos 24 super chat eh llevamos la
halfway there we'll get to the
mitad llegaremos al
audio we'll get to the audio I'll put the
audio llegaremos al audio os pondré el
audio on for you Look what it says in the report
audio Mira lo que me pone en el reporte
eh this user is  re-uploading my
eh este usuario está resubiendo mi
content adding their own
contenido agregándole su propia marca de
watermark and profiting at the expense of my image
agua y lucr a Costa de mi imagen
affecting the monetization of my
afectando a la monetización de mi
content by partially summarizing it on
contenido al resumirlo parcialmente en
another
otra
platform affecting the monetization
plataforma afectando a la monetización
of my
de mi
content and
contenido y
profiting because I don't know how many visits
lucr pues no sé cuántas visitas tendría
the tweet would have I don't know if I get paid 300 bucks from
el twit no sé si cobro 300 pavos de
Twitter eh I get
Twitter eh yo al
300 bucks a month from Twitter and because I have
mes 300 pavos de Twitter y porque tengo
100 million visits
100 millones de visitas
Well I don't know how much your tweet is nimu
Pues no sé cuánto será tu tweet nimu
but if you want I'll give it to you eh I felt
pero si quieres te lo doy eh me ha dado
sorry about this that it's
pena esto de que de que te esté
affecting your monetization
afectando la monetización
partially affecting the monetization
parcialmente afectando la monetización
of my
de mi
content
contenido
pathetic and well it didn't stop
patético y bueno no se quedó la cosa
there after a
ahí al
while I find
rato me encuentro
What another one has taken down
Con qué ha tumbado
after a while in the afternoon he took down
otro al rato por la tarde ha tumbado
another one, I mean he started looking for this it's
otro o sea se ha puesto a buscar esto es
one from December 20th, I mean he
uno del 20 de diciembre o sea se ha
started looking for his name Let's see how many
puesto a buscar su nombre A ver cuántos
clicks I would get on my Twitter account
click tendría yo en mi cuenta de Twitter
and let's see if he would throw my account
y a ver si me tiraba la cuenta
here people give me a TT from delos
aquí me pone la gente un TT de delos
when Dallas reported a
cuando Dallas le reportó un
video Dallas why don't you want
vídeo Dallas por qué no quieres que la
people  watch this
gente vea este
video is in Juan
vídeo está en modo Juan
joblo mode I'm really
joblo yo es que de verdad que te
telling you things why don't you want
digo dasas por qué no quieres que la
people to see this video
gente vea este vídeo
man they do everything that what they criticize
tío hacen todo lo que lo que critican
eh they do everything that and the crazy one that I told myself About the
eh hacen todo lo que y el loquito que me
crazy one I have already done a ratio the
loquito ya le he hecho un ratio al
crazy one they say to
loquito le dicen a
with girls from Ah well This he told
con niñas de Ah bueno Esto me lo dijo a
me no that I was talking to that that I was
mí no que yo hablaba con que que yo era
a groomer he told me eh the inmate and
un groomer me dijo eh el el recluso y le
someone says proof r and Put an account here
dice alguien pruebas r y Pon aquí una
and accusing me of grooming and it's like this
e acusándome de grooming y es como esto
what the [ __ ] does it have to do
qué [__] tiene que ver
with me I mean this was a girl who was around
conmigo o sea esto era una chica que
here in the chat
estaba por aquí por el chat de manera
regularly and she was in the group kids
habitual y estaba en el grupo chavalería
and they put me Here a t in which I
y me ponen Aquí un t en el que yo le
say I'll eat your face I'll eat your face
digo te como tu cara te como tu cara
repression that is something that I tell you Here
represi oa que es algo que os digo Aquí
to all when you send me super chat
a todos cuando me mandáis super chat
when you put me something
cuando me ponéis algo
nice damn There is no connotation
bonito [__] No hay ninguna connotación
Eh murky how do you want to give it
Eh turbia como ustedes le queréis dar
Well in fact the one who started with
Bueno de hecho el que el que empezó con
this roll already has a lawsuit And you already
este rollo ya tiene una demanda Y ya lo
know the second one on the way the second  on the
sabe la segunda en camino la segunda en
way to see if the [ __ ]
camino a ver si llega la [__]
first one arrives you forgot to put what happened yesterday
primera te faltó poner lo de ayer de
before seeing
antes de ver a
him everything was based on the insecurity
el todo venía en base a la inseguridad
that I had but this What is it last night
que yo tenía pero esto Qué es anoche
luare last night he started doing a live
luare anoche se puso a hacer un directo
talking about
hablando de
Dallas I said no what I said neither a
Dallas dije no esto que dije tampoco un
kiss
beso
mica last night he put on a live on Christmas Eve
mica anoche se puso en nochebuenas un
talking about
directo hablando de
Dallas to
Dallas para
fall
caera
stupid urar with 100% veracity that
estúpida urar con 100% de veracidad de
I am a very different person
que soy una persona bastante diferente
wismi you still think it's God Let's see you didn't
wismi te sigue pareciendo God A ver no
insult but you asked a question that
insultaste pero hiciste una pregunta que
could if I answer it one way or
puede si es que la contesto de cierta u
another could get me into one a kiss
otra manera puede meterme en una un beso
Hey we're 26 eh They're already more than
Oye llevamos 26 eh Ya llevan más de la
halfway through controversy I mean clearly you're
mitad polémica o sea claramente estás
looking for something interesting And although I could give an
buscando chicha Y aunque podría dar una
answer that doesn't bother anyone I'm not
respuesta que no moleste a nadie no te
going to give it to you just because you
la voy a dar solamente por el hecho que
're looking for controversy I'm seeing your
estás buscando polémica estoy viendo tus
ulterior motives So no I'm not going
dobles intenciones Entonces no no te voy
to answer you but just so I don't give you
a contestar pero solamente para no darte
the pleasure I saw How people were looking at you
el gusto yo vi Cómo gente te miraba
before it became when you updated it's
antes se volvió cuando actualizaste es
the Avatar I don't know the truth there are many there are
el Avatar no sé la verdad hay muchas hay
many reasons why people
muchas razones por las que la gente me
got a mania for me and  I still get mania
agarró Manía y me sigue agarrando Manía
to this day
a día de hoy
eh nothing nimu for nothing eh For nothing
eh nada nimu por nada eh Por nada
nimu I don't understand
nimu No entiendo el Por
why it's very complex the truth is it's a subject
qué es muy complejo la verdad es un tema
of complex sociology and I, I know that I
de sociología compleja e yo yo sé que no
'm not to everyone's taste
soy plato de buen gusto para todo el
eh And with that I settle I mean it was
mundo eh Y con eso me conformo o sea era
something that before I couldn't get over like
algo que antes yo no podía superar tipo
I said why are there people who don't like me at all no
Yo decía por qué hay gente que no le
idea why and now it's like I don't give a damn
nada ni idea Por qué y ahora es como me
and I snort at it
la me la sopla y me la resopla
completely like I think it
rotundamente onda Yo creo que también
was also because of the lack of self-love that I
fera por la falta de amor propio que
wanted to be loved like love me because I don't
quería que me amen tipo ámenme porque no
love myself eh the famous
me amo a mí misma eh las famosas
deficiencies that we talk about many
carencias de las que hablamos muchas
times that make us look for
veces que hacen que busquemos las
solutions in places where it doesn't
soluciones en lugares donde no
correspond instead of within ourselves
corresponde en vez de nuestro interior
I hope that Win that trial against adas has already
Espero que Gan ese juicio contra adas ya
received what he deserves no I can't
ha de recibir su merecido no no puedo
say anything because I'm in the middle of that
decir nada porque estoy en medio de eso
but don't worry that everything is fine Okay delo
pero tranquilo que está todo Bueno delo
in fact put a Claro Look I'm going to
de hecho puso un Claro Mira os voy a
tell you one
decir una
thing I'm going to tell you one thing but it is that
cosa os voy a decir una cosa pero es
I could be
que es que me puedo
wrong but well like delos has
equivocar pero bueno como delos ha
put in public a  thing luar Please
puesto en público una cosa luar Me pones
give me the link to Delos' Twitter
porfi el link del Twitter de delos
please so I don't leak
porfi para no filtrar Yo
anything I don't care but you know the impression
nada pero a mí sabéis la impresión que
I get that they haven't sued a [ __ ] thing
me da de que no han demandado una [__]
the impression I get is that they haven't
a mí la impresión que me dan es que no
sued a [ __ ] thing they have
han demandado una [__] [__] han
sent a burofax asking Dallas to
mandado un burofax pidiendole a Dallas
ret what Luis gendera did to me
que se ret lo que me hizo Luis gendera
a kiss Luis
un beso Luis
Look paripe nimu is the least indicated
Mira paripe nimu es la menos indicada
to talk about
para hablar de
puppies Merry Christmas gorgeous Greetings
perritos Feliz Navidad guapísimo Saludos
from ripo hearts two hearts is a
desde ripo corazones dos coraz es
Halloween pumpkin my goodness
calabaza de Halloween madre mía el
delox's Twitter is from Dallas eh I mean delox's
Twitter de delox es de Dallas eh o sea
Twitter is Look
el Twitter de delox es Mira
eh with utbh there has been talk because they have
eh con utbh que se ha hablado porque se
started to mess with Dallas a
han puesto a meterse con el Dallas un
kiss I think utbh will not end up having a
beso yo creo que utbh no acabará
relationship with this event there will be
teniendo relación con est evento tendrá
cordiality but apart from that I mean I don't
una cordialidad pero aparte o sea yo no
consider tbh I want to not consider him of
considero tbh quiero no considerarlo de
the same caliber as Delo and Ricky he
la misma calaña que el delo y el Ricky
would disappoint me amaris a kiss
me haría una decepción amaris un beso
By the way eh
Por cierto eh
Although this one is
Aunque este sea
bald very beautiful eh very beautiful that she is very
calvo guapísima eh guapísima que está
beautiful that the girlfriend of
guapísima que está la novia de
utbh I don't know how much longer a kiss
utbh no sé cuánto le queda un beso
Alex delo's Twitter It's about Dallas
Alex el Twitter de delo Es sobre Dallas
eh Look miare posted something about Dallas
eh Mira miare ha puesto algo de Dallas
no well that Dallas followers
no bueno que los seguidores de Dallas
have insulted in a message no later we'll
han insultado en un mensaje no luego lo
see if anything he made an account that
veremos si acaso hecho una cuenta que se
messed with pambi Merry Christmas this month
meto con pambi Feliz Navidad este mes
I make aos handsome How are you a kiss Mar no no no no he's not
hago aos guapo Cómo estás un beso Mar no
here because he met her because he
no no no esta porque la conoció porque
met her here debating with me and he's a
la conoció aquí debatiendo conmigo y es
hater of D the
hater de D la
chick this about
tipa esto sobre
pambi 31000 likes this tweet from nimu
pambi 31000 likes este twet de nimu
come on I don't believe that ji vina a
vamos eso no me lo creo ji vina un
kiss 31000 likes this t of n no
beso 31000 likes este t de n ni de
way your channel It's about dala No man my
coña tu canal Es sobre dala No hombre mi
channel what the [ __ ] is going to be about dala my
canal qué [__] va a ser sobre dala mi
channel Today he's talking about Dallas because
canal Hoy está hablando de Dallas porque
nimu and delo have started talking about
nimu y delo han puesto a hablar de
Dallas if nimu and delox don't talk about Dallas
Dallas si nimu y delox no hablan de
I don't know nor here that we talk about
Dallas yo no sé ni aquí que hablamos de
Dallas if Dallas right now wasn't
Dallas si Dallas ahora mismo no estaba
involved in anything or anything like that
metido en ninguna cosa ni nada por el
But well
estilo Pero bueno
what
e qué
was it Ah yes yes yes I know what he wanted and to
era Ah sí sí sí ya sé lo que quería y
see
ver
but I haven't seen it he
pero no lo he visto lo ha
deleted it  32,000 likes this doesn't have a
borrado 32000 likes esto que no tiene ni
damn thing Look 112,000 112,000 likes
de coña Mira 112.000 112000 likes tuvo
my exclusive about
en Twitter mi exclusiva del divorcio de
Ari and Juan's divorce had on Twitter and these people are trying to tell me
Ari y Juan y me están queriendo decir
that the fake reval of animu
esta gente que el fake reval de animu
has the same thing
tiene lo mismo
what tweet it
qué tweet
was he deleted it luare it was a tweet where it
fue lo ha borrado luare era un tet donde
said something about Dallas pick up the burofax
decía algo de Dallas recoge los burofax
pick up the burofax
recoge los burofax
exactly it has more likes it has more
exactamente tiene más likes tiene más
likes the tweets that you visit the podcast
likes los tweet que visitas el podcast
I find it weird but oh well I don't know maybe it's that on
yo lo veo rarete pero bueno no lo sé a
Twitter
lo mejor es que en Twitter se
his tweets are highly recommended
recomiendan mucho sus
dude there was a
tweets tío había un
tweet that he said Dallas pick up the
tweet que él decía Dallas coge los
burofax This look
burofax Este mira
bmark has eliminated pambi
bmark ha eliminado pambi la semana
last week I met with the ceo of bmark and I
pasada me reuní con el ceo de bmark y
took the opportunity to explain what happened with
aproveché para exponerle lo ocurrido con
pambi it's that you Imagine this guy
pambi es que tú Imagínate este tío
talking about pambi everywhere By the
hablando de pambi en todas partes Por
way Daniel less threesomes Why less
cierto Daniel menos tríos Por qué menos
threesomes Why Alex a kiss and more take
tríos Por qué Alex un beso y más [__]
the burofax what are you afraid of midón I
los burofax de qué tienes miedo midón o
mean and more take the burofax if you file
sea y más [__] los burofax si tú pones
a lawsuit you don't you  If you don't send a
una demanda tú no tú no mandas un
burofax,
burofax
then what I get the impression
entonces a mí lo que me da la impresión
is that these people will be
es de que esta gente le andarán
trying to send a burofax to Dallas, one of
intentando mandar burofax a Dallas de
those burofaxes. If you don't apologize, we'll sue
esos burofax del palo si no pides Perdón
you,
te ponemos una demanda
huh. It seems to me like, what's that?
eh A mí me da la impresión de Qué es eso
Huh? He hasn't sued, so he's going to
eh No ha demandado qué va a poner una
sue in
demanda en
Dubai. It seems to me that that's
Dubai a mí me da la impresión de que es
it, huh. If he's saying, "Go pick up the burofaxes there," it does
eso eh si está diciendo ahí recoge los
n't make
no tiene
sense. What happens if he gives the headquarters and
sentido Qué pasa si da la sede y pide
apologizes, huh. Let's
perdón
see.
eh A ver
Well, I don't know what would happen
Pues yo no sé lo que pasaría
regarding that issue of the dog, it
em respecto al tema ese de lo del perro
's not what she wants to sue. No,
no es lo que ella quiere demandar no lo
what Dallas told her about the dog, what her
que le dijo Dallas de lo del perro que
ex told her is that, you know, that's very
ex es que ya sabéis que eso es muy
subjective. What one judge tells you yes,
subjetivo que lo que un juez te dice que
another tells you no. So I don't know what would
sí otro te dice no Entonces no lo sé lo
happen. The first thing is for
que pasaría lo primero es que le llegue
the lawsuit to reach him. The first thing is for him to
la demanda lo primero es que la lo
sue in Dubai. Of course, he should sue in
demande en Dubai Claro que lo demande en
Dubai and and what, and that it has a track record in
Dubai y y que y que tenga recorrido en
Dubai, of course,
Dubai claro se tiene que valorar el
the things that Nimu says about him have to be assessed.
valorar las cosas que nimu dice de él
Also,
también
no  insults that have been said
no insultos que se hayan dicho
to each other and the
mutuamente y se tendrá que valorar la
veracity or not of what I do not know must be
veracidad o no de lo que no sé se tiene
assessed. Every man has to look, it's one
que valorar todo hombre a ver es una
thing to tell someone that you
cosa lo de decirle a alguien que te
sleep with a dog, not that you [ __ ] a
acuestas con perro no que te follas a un
dog or that or that you have slept with a dog, he did
perro o que o que te has acostado con un
not tell him No, that he slept with
perro no le dijo No que se acostaba con
a dog. No man, of course, that
un perro No hombre claro eso
is obviously actionable if you
evidentemente es demandable si se lo
tell someone for free. Yes, it is worth it
sueltas a alguien gratuitamente Sí vale
now in the context that they have of
ahora en el contexto que ellos tienen de
war, man. I believe that Nimu has
guerra hombre Yo creo que nimu ha
shared things where he calls the other a
compartido cosas donde al otro lo llama
pedophile and things like that, so that would be
pedófilo y cosas por el estilo entonces
assessed if you are in a dispute
valoraría si tú estás en una contienda
with a person in which you are
con una persona en la que tú le estás
calling one a pedophile and the other
diciendo a uno pedófilo y el otro te
tells you that you have slept with a dog.
dice que te has acostado con un perro
Well, I don't know what would
Pues no sé yo qué
happen, you understand
pasaría me entiendes
what I'm saying, I'm not a fortune teller.
qué te digo no soy adivino yo
Personally, if I am telling a
personalmente si le estoy diciendo a una
person that he is a groomer and a
persona que es un groomer y un
scammer, well, I am not going to sue him
estafador pues no lo voy a demandar
because the next day he will tell me that I am a son
porque al día siguiente él me diga hijo
of a [ __ ] or that I can [ __ ] a goat. What do you
de [__] o que me folle una cabra Qué
want me to tell you in the first place
quieres que te diga en primer lugar
because  I was a little upset, I'm
porque me suría un poco los [__]
also telling you,
también te digo
eh perfect, I'm dealing with that issue right now
eh perfecto estoy ahora mismo con ese
and no, I don't know, even if I sue a
tema y no no sé hasta yo demando a una
person who continues day to day, I mean, one thing is that
persona que sigue al día a día o sea una
you
cosa es que tú
[Music]
[Música]
m one thing is that you had a
m una cosa es que tú hayas tenido un
conflict with a person, okay, eh
conflicto con una persona vale
in 2022, okay, you in 2022
eh en el 2022 vale tú en el 2022 has
had a conflict with a person, you
tenido un conflicto con una persona os
insulted each other, okay, if I
habéis insultado mutuamente vale si yo
sue that person for the insults they
demando a esa persona por los insultos
made me in the days after that, it
que me haga los días posteriores a eso
's obviously a rhetorical spirit Kendy, no, and they're
evidentemente es ánimo retor Kendy no y
not going to condemn him. Of course, but man,
no le van a condenar Claro pero hombre
if that person continues to insult you
si esa persona sigue insultándote
strongly
fuertemente
during all the weeks of 2023 and
durante Todas las semanas del 2023 y
during all the weeks of 2024,
durante Todas las semanas de 2024 hombre
well, I think that what
pues ahí Creo que no le va a valer lo
I said in 2022 won't be worth it, eh, I think, eh, I think,
que yo le haya dicho en 2022 eh creo eh
but well, there are people who
creo pero bueno hay personas que se
believe that, eh, there are people who
creen que sí eh Hay personas que se
believe that because I told you, I don't know, that in
creen que porque yo te dije no sé que en
2022 it will be useful to you, that it's like it's
el 2022 te va a servir para que tú es
carte blanche for you to
que es una carta blanca para que tú
say whatever you want  2022 2023
digas lo que tú quieras el 2022 el 2023
2024 and now we start on the 25th And
el 2024 y y ahora Empezamos el 25 Y
of course I don't think so, I don't think so
claro me da a mí que no eh me da a mí
but well, each one
que no pero bueno cada uno cada uno que
does what they can take on,
que haga lo que lo que pueda asumir
period, I can talk so not everything is
punto puedo hablar así que no esta todo
okay with Dallas that the two of them came out to talk
bien con Dallas que salieron a hablar
together, wow, there are times when I say,
los dos juntos buah hay veces que digo
hey, everyone found out about this, how
Che todo el mundo se enteró de esto qué
bad or how good or whatever and I say
mal o qué bien o lo que sea y y digo no
there aren't people who live in a bubble or or or
hay gente que vive en una burbuja o o o
well or luckily they don't find out about
bueno o por suerte no se entera de las
things because sometimes I say how envious
cosas porque yo a veces digo qué envidia
of people How envious of people who
de la gente Qué envidia de la gente que
don't get into controversies or find out about
no se mete en polémicas ni se entera en
controversies or anything I mean, today I
polémicas ni nada O sea a día de hoy Yo
am that person but I don't give a damn about
soy esa persona pero me chupan un huevo
all the controversies eh but of course there are
todas las polémicas eh pero claro hay
people who are on an
gente que que que está red
outdated network, the Lore, I prefer to have my
desactualizada el Lore prefiero tener mi
community, people who don't give a
comunidad gente que le le sople una
damn about the controversy than who
[__] la la polémica que que que le
care because, let's see, I'm going to accept both of them,
importe porque a ver ambos los voy a
those who also said that
aceptar a los que ler también dijo que
Javi did have information  privileged
Javi sí tenía información privilegiada
by the 10,000 well nothing happens ler is going to
por los 10.000 bueno no pasa nada ler va
deliver a tweet of mine from
ha entregar un tweet mío del
2022 it will surely turn out well he
2022 seguramente le le salga bien le
likes gossip and those who don't but eh I
gusta el salseo y a los que no pero eh o
mean even if it doesn't seem like it to me I hate
sea aunque no parezca a mí yo odio el
gossip both that of others and that I
salseo tanto el de los demás como que me
win it Ah o o me being in the middle of
lo Gan a mí Ah o o yo estar en medio de
gossip because it's horrible it's
un salseo porque es horrible es es
horrible and on the other hand I'm not
horrible y por otro lado A mí no me
interested in other people's lives I
interesa la vida de las demás personas o
mean don't you you you We have 30 out of 50
sea no me tú t tú Tenemos 30 de 50
eh how good the people who don't get into
eh qué bien la gente que no se mete en
controversy proceed to delete your hijja
polémica procede a borrarle tu hijja a
Javi No no yes tell your crack
Javi No no sí cuentes tua crack a mí
what do I care about the controversy of the reborn
queé me importa la polémica del reborn
with a cat with auron Play that I don't know what
con gata con auron Play que no sé qué le
happened to b I don't give a damn and half
pasó con b me chupa un huevo y la mitad
of the other What do people do with their lives I
del otro Qué hace la gente con sus vidas
mean turn off the Radio Dude one thing
o sea apagada la Radio Amigo yo una cosa
that really pisses me off is that for
que me da mucha bronca es que por
example someone asks in a
ejemplo alguien pregunta en un
comment says why funana nimu or
comentario pone por qué funana nimu o
why are they so angry with nimu or
por qué están tan enojados con nimu o
for I don't know what about nim and there's always that
por no sé qué de nim y Nunca falta el
little guy who says one of these
chaboncito que dice alguna de estas
things because this fó a lot of people Oh
cosas porque esta fó mucha gente Oh
Because he ruined the career
Porque arruinó la carrera
Alex
Alex
31 19 super chat and I'm putting an
31 19 super chat y os pongo un
audio it would be the first and only
audio sería el primer y único
audio that I'm going to advance of the rewind
audio que voy a adelantar del rewind
eh if we arrive eh that I still have my
eh si llegamos eh que todavía tengo mis
doubts eh of
dudas eh
many youtubers committed
de muchísimas youtubers cometió crimenes
war crimes in his life to pass was Hitler no I
de guerra en su vida pasar era Hitler no
mean There's always one who's going to
O sea Nunca falta uno que va a
misinform with lies So that
desinformar con mentiras Entonces eso me
bothered me a lot because I said I said
molestaba mucho porque decía yo decía
dude they're going to lie blatantly with
loco van a mentir descaradamente con
all those things and I can't do
todas esas cosas y yo no puedo hacer
anything because if I answer him I'm
nada porque si le contesto le estoy
giving
dando
attention if I answer them I'm paying
atención si les contesto estoy lando
attention and trying to take down the
atención y intentando tirarme la cuenta
Twitter account there's sure to be people
de Twitter seguro que hayde ya de gente
talking about it I mean it's eh
hablando de eso o sea es que eh
come on I'm risking my neck
vamos me juego el cuello
come on of
vamos
course Javi Olive this guy is an [ __ ]
claro Javi Olive este tío es [__]
tesa What's up honey this guy is an
tesa Qué pasa corazón este tío es
[ __ ] eh jav oliveira is exposed
[__] eh jav oliveira es expuesto
as a censor and puts here again these
como censurador y pone aquí otra vez las
bad accounts of the [ __ ]
cuentas malitas estas de los [__]
balls saying that I have taken down that
[__] diciendo que yo he tumbado que
I  I haven't taken down a [ __ ] thing I
yo no he tumbado una [__] [__] que yo
don't take down anything but how am I going to take
no tumbo nada pero que yo cómo voy a
down anything because I never throw anything away
tumbar nada que yo no tiro nada nunca
dude really This is a [ __ ]
tío de verdad Este es un [__]
[ __ ] with three pairs of balls eh Let's
[__] de tres pares de [__] eh A
see this one What is an idiot dude What the [ __ ] am I
ver este Qué es idiota tío Para qué [__]
going to throw if I don't want them to stop
voy a tirar si yo no quiero que paren de
talking about
hablar de
me there is no there is no worse idea than to
mí es que no hay no hay peor idea que
make sure that nobody talks about me that
ponerte a que no hablen de mí nadie que
this one doesn't talk about me that the other one doesn't
este no hable de mí que el otro no me
mention my
mencione más
name anymore But of course people
nombre Pero por supuesto que la gente
understood that I don't know why he didn't
entendió que yo no sé por qué n le llegó
talk to Javi on any occasion
a hablar a Javi en alguna oportunidad
why Because even before d
por qué Porque incluso antes de que d se
messed with nimu Javi already messed
metiera con nimu Javi ya antes se metía
with nimu he was angry with him he was angry
con nimu le tenía rabia le tenía cólera
So I don't know he forgave him and that's it but oh
Entonces no sé lo perdonó y ya pero
well it was like he knew that oh really
bueno como que se sabía que ay de verdad
if it is already a kiss how are you Thank you very much it
si es que ya un beso qué tal Muchísimas
is predictable now what he's going to
gracias es previsible ya lo que va a
say dude for free when he's going to
decir tío gratuitamente cuando lo va a
see it well he's going to see it [ __ ] great that
ver bien lo va a ver de [__] madre que
the cl Look causes the result thing I
los cl Mira provoca el resultado cosa yo
also criticize people who put
también critico a las personas que ponen
Twitch and then  they take a picture or they back
Twitch y luego se retratan o se echan
out and end up deleting their tweet, I
para atrás y terminan borrando su tweet
mean, I don't know why they do it. The
o sea no sé para qué lo hacen yo las
only times I've deleted a tweet have
únicas veces que he borrado tweet ha
been when I've had
sido cuando he tenido faltas
spelling mistakes because of the [ __ ]
ortográficas por [__]
author, what memeable faces XD
autor prop qué caras tan memeables XD
badly stated So nothing more but
enunciado mal Entonces lo nada más pero
that these people do it all the time Juan
que esta gente lo hace a cada rato Juan
guarnizo auron's mother Play now
guarnizo la madre de auron Play ahora
nimu too Well let's see what tweet he
nimu también Bueno vamos a ver qué twet
put people I see it as if
le puso gente lo veo como para que el
Javi oliveira himself would see it in that case you
mismo Javi oliveira lo vea en tal caso
would have written to him privately Although
le hubieses escrito al privado Aunque
Javi might have leaked it too
igual Javi lo hubiese filtrado también
Ah Why are you deleting it now, here is this
Ah Para qué lo borras ya aquí está esto
what people say they came to clarify a
qué dice la peñita vino a matizar un
clip where they pointed out Dallas as
clip donde señalaban a Dallas de
bullying more B that he invents Cos c the
bullying má B que inventa Cos c la
death of serene the channel deleted for
muerte de serene se canal borrado por
thumbnails seven collaborations with
miniaturas siete colaboraciones con
puppies for now I'm going the fridge
perritos de momento voy el frigor se
deserves a video in my image a few
merece ya un video en mi imagen unos
euros it seems that things are
eurillos que parece que está la cosa
bad in the fridge because of my
chunga en el frigorífico por culpa de mi
clip Merry Christmas this user is
clip Feliz Navidad este usuario está
re-uploading my content adding their
resubiendo mi contenido agregándole su
own watermark and profiting from  The cost of
propia marca de agua y lucr a Costa de
my image affecting the monetization of
mi imagen afectando a la monetización de
my content by partially summarizing it
mi contenido al resumirlo parcialmente
on another platform Well at least he didn't
en otra plataforma Bueno al menos no
say that you're watching a Marvel movie
dijo que estas mirando una película de
no [ __ ] he is an [ __ ]
no [__] es
dude he has to fit it in
[__] tío tiene que meter por
Well but Dalas but
calzador Bueno pero Dalas pero
Dallas I was in favor of
Dallas yo cuá estaba a favor de que
Dallas throwing I don't know what I don't know how much
Dallas tire no sé qué no sé cuánto
I'm an [ __ ] but he has to
yo [__] pero es que él tiene que
please that he has to be true
agradar a eso él tiene que verad
pathetic So how is it that it
patético Entonces cómo de que eso me
stops bothering me for the simple fact of
deje de molestar por el simple hecho de
what you but see I don't throw a [ __ ]
lo que vos pero ve Yo no tiro una [__]
[ __ ] Look this is a channel dedicated to
[__] Mira esto es un canal dedicado a
me this is a channel where I put a
mí esto es un canal de que yo pongo un
tweet and there's a video of that tweet okay
tweet y hay un vídeo de ese tweet vale
eh what am I going to throw me put whatever I
eh que voy a tirar yo que ponga lo que
want put whatever I want my nice
quiera que ponga lo que quiera m buenas
tits Dalas
tetitas Dalas
makes his own rigu in Hispanic and here he will
hace su propio rigu en Hispano y aquí
surely have said Ah well well you were
seguramente habrá dicho Ah pues pues tú
messing with Alex cool I don't know what he has to
te metías con Alex molón no sé qué tiene
like you know if he doesn't even know
que agradar sabes si es que no sabe ni
eh the times that I've seen him it's that he doesn't
siquiera eh las veces que lo he visto es
even have an opinion because
que ni siquiera tiene una opinión porque
no no he doesn't know what to think Because if he gives an opinion
no no no sabe qué opinar Porque si opina
maybe he  contradicts the day
a puede que se contradiga con el día
before well anyway a fan just
anterior bueno en fin un fan acaba de
said Omar Because if the kid who
decir Omar Porque si el pibe que
asked why F an animu goes to
preguntó por que F un an animu va a la
reality and contrasts the information that they're
realidad y contrasta esa información que
giving him, that is to say the guy goes to
le están dando es decir el chavón va a
Google and searches and finds out well about me that's what
Google y busca y Averigua bien sobre mí
a person with criteria would do
que eso haría una persona con criterio
a person with common sense would grab
una persona con sentido común agarraría
and search this is true Oh it was a lie I do
y buscaría esto es verdad Oh era mentira
n't know what I don't know how much to contrast it you
no sé qué no sé cuánto lo contrastar me
understand it would be a person that I
entendés sería una persona que yo
would want in my community but if that
quisiera mi comunidad pero si esa
person stays with a
persona se queda con un comentario
stupid comment from someone who is
estúpido de alguien que le está
deliberately lying to him and it's a
mintiendo deliberadamente y es un
broken telephone with that He is a
teléfono descompuesto con ello Es una
person that I am interested in my community
persona que me interese en mi comunidad
anyway because he doesn't even have
de todas maneras porque no tiene ni
a minimum of common sense
siquiera un mínimo de sentido común como
to look for the information on his own
para buscar la información por su cuenta
So at that moment it stopped
Entonces en ese momento me dejó de
bothering me or rather it stopped bothering me that so much
molestar o sea me dejó de molestar que
that they lie about me that
tanto que mientan sobre de mí que la
people believe it Because both those who
gente se lo crea Porque tanto los que
lie and those who believe it are
mienten como los que se lo creen están
of the same ilk, I mean they are people who are
en la misma calaña o sea son gente que
not informed and and who annoy just for the sake of it
no Se informa y y que jode por [__]
but you know what the worst thing is that these
pero sabes que es lo peor que estos
rumors are spread by people who  has
rumores los difunde gente que no tiene
followers just like Pepito 54 with
seguidores igual qu es Pepito 54 con
three followers and goes and says hey cheer up, I'm scamming I
tres seguidores y va lece y dice eh nimo
don't know what I am bro but you know
estafó No sé qué yo bro pero vos sabes
that there is something more important places
que est hay algo más importante lugares
than this is that I get a little lazy
de esto es que me da un poco de pereza
cheer up the truth is that it's like if
animo la verdad que es como si es que
this is no longer it's not that I already lived this it's that
esto ya no no es que esto ya lo viví es
n it's like he gets really into
que n es como que se raya mucho con las
things he gives things a lot of thought you
cosas le da muchas vueltas a las cosas
know it's done it's done a lot with
sabes se hace se hace mucho con las
stories you know He gets really into it with fu
historias sabes Se raya mucho con fú
trust you spending Christmas Eve
fíate tú echarte la Nochebuena
trying to take over
intentando tirarle la cuenta de Twitter
Javi Oliveira's Twitter account G How are you How are you
a Javi oliveira G Cómo estás Cómo estás
gentlemen 28 at 8 in the evening I'm counting
señores 28 a las 8 de la tarde cuento
on you all eh guys
con todos ustedes eh cabrones
what a lazy girl better change the
qué pereza de muchacha mejor cambia de
subject we change the subject I'm counting on
tema cambiamos de tema cuento con todos
you all on the 28th at 8
ustedes el día 28 a las 8
okay on the
vale el
28th at 8 in the evening I'm premiering on the
día 28 a las 8 de la tarde estreno en el
main channel that's 14 super chats left for
principal eso faltan 14 super chat para
me to put a clip
que os ponga un clip
Okay 14 super chats left for me to
Vale faltan 14 super chat para que os
put a clip let's go a clip not an audio
ponga un clip vamos un clip no un audio
an audio of one of the clips okay  it's going to
un audio de uno de los clips vale va a
be the first and only clip that I'm going to
ser el primer y único clip que voy a O
So I'm going to put up okay the first and
sea que voy a poner vale el primer y
only audio that I'm going to give you in advance but
único audio que os voy a adelantar pero
so you can act like men today I'm going to give you a little
para que os hagáis hombre hoy os
preview Hey how many viewers do you think you'll get Well I don't know they believed it honestly I hope so I don't know I don't know no the clin no Ezequiel Pati a kiss the clin no because I want you to enjoy it there I want you to enjoy it live but I want you to listen to the
directo pero quiero que escuchéis el el
audio so you can hear the talent Okay there are
audio para que escuchéis el talento Vale
13 super chats left I'm going to the bathroom in a
faltan 13 super chat voy al baño un
second eh I don't even wash my
segundo eh No me lavo ni las
hands
manos
al al
al al
How nice it would be to hide in that room
Qué rico sería esconderse en ese cuarto
and watch all day Javi damn you guys
y observar todo el día Javi [__] qué
are so shady
turbio sois
how shady I am [ __ ] my hairspray is
cabrones qué turbio soy [__] se me ha
gone and you can't see my bangs no let's
ido la laca y no ve el flequillo no a
see
ver
guys in 13 super
chicos dentro de 13 super
chat in 13 super chat
chat dentro de 13 super chat
we'll hear a preview
escuchamos un adelanto
you've put up 50 super chats again
has vuelto a poner 50 super chat
Knowing how stiff we are Javi damn
Sabiendo lo tiesos que somos Javi [__]
but stiff eh guys besides it is  that in
pero tiesos eh cabrones además es que en
the youth they are worth less the
la chavalería valen menos
super chat are worth less eh or so
los los super chat valen menos eh o sea
this 50 super chat in the
esto 50 super chat en la
[Music]
[Música]
gentlemen luar now
señoreros luar ahora
a kiss
un beso
Blue what do we see
Blue qué vemos
now that of r the crazy one let's see what
ahora lo de r el loquito a ver qué le
happens to the crazy one r explodes with gibel But
pasa al loquito r explota con gibel Pero
where is this clown this lauk Uruguayan
dónde está el payasín este lauk uruguaya
Poor thing hon Poor thing a m he really is crazy
Pobrecita hón Pobrecita a m de verdad
eh he is crazy he is crazy
está loquito eh
he thinks that he
está loquito está loquito él cree que él
thinks that he really is based but it's a
cree que de verdad es basado pero da una
shame Look at you piece of loser to
lástima Mira pedazo de fracasado para
see if he continues taking money from the
ver si sigue sacándole plata a los
otacos to see if one day you move to
otacos a ver si algún día te mues a la
your mom's house he starts following a
casa de tu mamá se pone a following a a
Javi the wig
Javi el peluca
guy aged 13 forever la was
tío de edad de 13 años forever la se
also called in another please minor
llamaba también en otro por favor menor
of age of 13 years for also another such
de edad de 13 años for tambén otro tal
said per this is gold est ler let's
decía per esto es oro est ler vamos a
see here at what moment me in my and old
ver aquí en qué momento yo en mi y viejo
tasty How did you do at Christmas I hope
sabroso Cómo te fue en Navidad Espero
well I just got to your live by
que bien Apenas llegue a tu directo de
pure chance because YouTube didn't
pura casualidad porque YouTube no me
notify me face throwing a kiss face
notificó cara lanzando un beso cara
throwing a  kiss a kiss comfortable comfortable I
lanzando un besoo un beso agustito
told lies you piece of clown
agustito dije mentiras pedazo de payaso
8 in the morning he stayed up at 8 in the
8 de la mañana se quedó a las 8 de la
morning until 8 in the morning oh
mañana hasta las 8 de la mañana oj
crying I wake up eye ask her
llorando despierto ojo pregúntele a la
right now Laurita can say it and can she it's
ahorita lo puede decir Laurita y pued la
not even be trust yourself how he changes the him
no es ni siquiera sea fíate tú có cambia
But this is this This is good
el el Pero esto se lo esto Esto bueno en
anyway I think it's more than obvious not that
fin yo creo que es más que obvio no que
this goes in the second demand of
que esto vaya en la segunda demanda de
lerl who is the one who suddenly
lerl que es el que de repente se ha
started saying this but I don't know
puesto a decir esto pero no sé el por
why but apart from giving it an obvious
qué pero aparte dándole un tinte obvio
laser tint no no but giving it a tint I
láser no no pero dándole un tinte me
stay up at 8 in the morning with
quedo a las 8 de la mañana despierto con
my son okay at that time it was
mi hijo vale que en aquella época eran
the first months of the
los primeros meses del
baby ah
bebé ah
what are we talking about Ah yes about
de qué estamos hablando Ah sí lo de las
8 in the morning [ __ ] cinema eh
8 de la mañana [__] cine eh
kids [ __ ] madness reaching 50 now
chavales [__] locura llegar ya a los 50
eh eh
eh
but you don't even have to explain
eh pero no tienes ni que explicar el Por
why Javi man But it's as simple
qué Javi hombre Pero es tan sencillo
as I'm commenting on it
como que lo estoy comentando en un
live you Imagine that I am grume
directo tú Imagínate que yo estoy grume
as they are saying Alex a kiss and
como están diciendo ellos Alex un beso y
I start talking  with all the
me pongo a hablar con toda la
naturalness in the world in a live
naturalidad del mundo en un directo
but I'm not going to repeat the
pero es que no voy a repetir más las
lawsuits that are filed, those that are for are
demandas que están puestas las que están
people who what can I tell you? I mean, yes, yes, it
son personas que qué te digo O sea si si
is the r has been in prison right now and
es el r ha estado ahora mismo recluso y
from ler l ler believes ler believes from what I
de ler l ler cree ler cree por lo que he
saw on twt today that when he gets to
visto en un twt hoy que él cuando llegue
trial he is going to explain that I put him
al juicio va a explicar que yo le puse
in 2020 I don't know what you can explain whatever
en 2020 no sé qué tú puedes explicar lo
you want about 2020 lerl okay I'm not
que tú quieras del 2020 lerl vale Yo no
going to take away any lawsuit or anything like that
te voy a quitar ninguna demanda ni nada
I'm not going to take away
por el estilo Yo no te voy a quitar
any lawsuit you would have to pay and you
ninguna demanda tendrías que pagar y
would have to apologize and you would have to
tendrías que pedir perdón y tendrías que
do many things that you are not going to do you go
hacer muchas cosas que no vas a hacerla
to trial you surrender because in
tú ve al juicio tú entrega que yo en el
2022 I messed with you I mean if you think
2022 me metí contigo o sea si tú crees
that you can explain that it's not that
que tú puedes explicar que no es que
look it's that in 2022 he put me You put what
mira es que en el 2022 me puso Tú pon lo
you see fit I tell you that
que tú veas conveniente Yo te digo a ti
yes, it will surely be worth it to you that
que sí que seguramente te va a valer que
in 2022 I told you I don't know what And you are going to
yo en el 2022 te dije no sé qué Y tú vas
be the  2023 Merry Christmas Javi
a estar el 2023 Feliz Navidad Javi
I hope you had a great time with
Espero que lo hayas pasado de 100 con
your loved ones A
tus seres queridos Un
kiss eye falt 2025 go on that we have not
beso ojo falt el 2025 anda que no hemos
spent the night talking because the dwarf did not
pasado noche hablando porque el enano no
sleep a wink and he knocked you down he dared to
pegaba ojos y os tumbaba osaba para
rest the first months yes he the the
descansar los primeros meses sí es que
boy you know how alanne is and
el el el chico tú sabes cómo es alanne y
he there what we did was eh At
el el ahí lo que hacíamos eraa eh Por la
night here here at this time I
noche aquí aquí en esta en esta época yo
would cut the extracts of the
me recortaba los extractos de la
salsería and and I would upload it and the whole roll back
salsería y y lo subía yo y todo el rollo
then what I did well I
ese entonces yo lo que hacía pues me
stayed chill at night I would cut
quedaba chill por la noche cortaba
cutting the extracts patatin patatan And I
cortando los extractos patatin patatán Y
kept the baby for myself in fact I think
el bebé me lo quedaba yo de hecho creo
that in many live shows eh you can see
que en muchos directos eh se ve ya
when I'm going to finish the live show and
cuando voy a terminar el directo ya
put the basket here no and I was awake chill
poner aquí el capacho no y yo estaba
Merry Christmas
despierto chil Feliz Navidad
jav We will continue smiling face but
jav Seguiremos cara sonriente pero es
what I'm telling you not even
que lo que te estoy diciendo ni siquiera
in the clip I'm saying that I would
en el clip estoy diciendo que yo me
stay at 8 in the morning talking to
pegara a las 8 de la mañana hablando con
the girl in the first place I don't know how
la chavala en primer lugar yo no sé la
old the girl is
edad que tiene la chavala
and I don't know  age that he is no we are not
e no sé la edad que tiene no no estamos
talking in a romantic or
hablando en un contexto amoroso ni
sexual context or anything Blue a kiss okay But
sexual ni nada Blue un beso vale Pero
this man This one is crazy lost
esto hombre Este está loquito perdido
but the fact is that this one lives in Spain this one
pero es que este vive en España este
lives in Spain already has a lawsuit and the one
vive en España ya tiene una demanda y la
from Dallas I don't know what the one from Dallas is going to put
del Dallas yo no sé qué va a poner la
because in mine she's going to claim that I
del Dallas porque en la mía va a alegar
messed with him in 2020 that I
que yo me metí con él 2020 que yo me
fought with him in 2022 when we were
peleé con él en 2022 cuando estábamos
fighting but boy that's what you're going to
peleándonos pero chico es que eso es lo
hand over You you to explain
que vas a entregar Tú tú para explicar
that you have been messing with me
que tú te has estado metiendo conmigo
with barbarities all of 2023 and all of
con barbaridades todo el 2023 y todo el
2024 face smiling with heart eyes
2024 cara sonriendo con ojos de corazón
face smiling with heart eyes face
cara sonriendo con ojos de corazón cara
throwing a kiss face throwing a kiss
lanzando un beso cara lanzando un beso
another contribution for the
otra aportación para el viejo más
tastiest old man YouTube Javi for when the
sabroso YouTube Javi para cuando el
Lego Simba face rolling with
Simba de Lego cara revolviéndose de la
laughter face rolling with laughter
risa cara revolviéndose de
Alex a kiss Hey there are seven more super
la Alex un beso Oye faltan siete super
chay nothing more eh like a good father
chay nada más eh que como un buen padre
helping no but it's not it's not about being a
ayudando no pero no es no se trata de
good father or a bad father it's about that
buen padre ni mal padre se trata de que
my job allows me I don't have a boss I
mi trabajo me lo permite no tengo jefe
don't have a schedule And then Lorena
no tengo horario Y entonces Lorena
was  very bitter I mean the child was
estaba muy amargada O sea la el niño era
my child is
el niño mío es
very nervous very very active Okay
muy nervioso muy muy activo Vale
then
entonces
Well at night I was there
Pues por la noche estaba yo ahí
awake chill you know maybe if she
despierto chill sabes a lo mejor si se
woke up well I put it here I
despertaba pues me lo ponía aquí me lo
put it here and and I was chill here I cut
ponía aquí y y estaba chill aquí cortaba
the extracts prepared scripts or something like that
los extractos preparaba guiones o así lo
whatever and in the morning when she
que sea y ya por la mañana cuando ella
woke up well I went to bed and I
se despertaba pues ya me acostaba yo y
fell asleep until noon
ya me quedaba dormido hasta el mediodía
whatever no e and we were talking in
lo que sea no e y estábamos hablando en
the group of course Well of course we were
el grupo claro Pues claro que estábamos
talking in the group where there was this
hablando en el grupo que estaba esta
girl Well of course there was this girl
chica Pues claro que estaba esta chica
I what the [ __ ] do I know no no no there was nothing
yo qué [__] sé no no no no había nada de
wrong with anyone being in the group
malo que estuviera nadie en el grupo
but since I don't know how old wale is and
pero como no sé la edad que tiene wale y
wale talks like an idiot talk wale
wale habla como un [__] hable wale
if he's not 11 years old wale or 13 because of the
si no tiene 11 años wale o 13 por los
mental chins the wale Huerta who is
chin mentales el wale Huerta que está
here donating no well it's true donate I don't
aquí donando no bueno es verdad dona No
think he has an
creo que
eye ask Laurita can tell you
tenga ojo pregúntele a Laurita lo puede
Laurita and
decir Laurita
Laurita doesn't remember can
y Laurita no se acuerda os lo puede
tell you Laurita and I don't know what other girl
decir Laurita y no sé qué otra chica
Of course well we're talking in the group
Claro pues estamos hablando en el grupo
Well, what we were talking about in the
pues lo que estuviéramos hablando en el
group that would surely be like the
grupo que seguramente sería como el
info kids I don't know what group it was if it
chavalería info no sé qué grupo era si
was the same as today no alne I don't
era el mismo de a día de hoy no alne no
know if it's the same Twitter group no
sé si es el mismo grupo de Twitter no
but it's that they say that I had
pero es que ellos dicen que yo tenía
shady conversations until so many at
conversaciones turbias hasta las tant de
night with a grume girl or rather
la noche con una chica grume o sea
look at you look at you la la la the
fíjate tú fíjate tú la la la la
transformation that they have given him truth Yes
transformación que le han dado verda Sí
yes he doesn't remember her name another
sí él no se acuerda cómo se llama otra
girl other girls sleepover he had
chica otras chicas pijamada hacía
sleepover on discord with 14 and
pijamada por discord con niñas de 14 y
13 year old girls this piece of old wanker
13 años el pedazo de viejo [__] este
no no no call I have never heard his
no no ninguna llamada no he escuchado su
voice in my life no I don't le no le I haven't
voz en la vida no Yo es que no le no le
even put a face to him I think eh And what the
no le he puesto ni cara creo yo eh Y qué
[ __ ] is he going to say that's what I said
[__] va a decir eso fue lo que yo dije
in my tweet what are they going to do Oh no what
en mi tweet qué van a hacer Oh no qué
accusation Abi you said that because of
acusación Abi dijiste que por culpa de
the forera they took away her internet
la forera le quitaron el internet
Laurita I would swear that this girl was the one they
Laurita yo juraría que esta chica fue la
then started harassing Calling the
que luego empezaron a a acosar Llamando
parents and such no this girl
a los a los padres y tal no esta chica
was not the same as the forera  they
no era la misma que la la forera se
started harassing her, calling her parents
pusieron a acosarla llamar a los padres
or something
o algo por el
God, what an accusation the
estilo Dios Qué acusación la pijamada
real sleepover was this fool doing, this
real hacía el bobo este el viejo
stupid old man, this one, and the other idiot because he
estúpido este y el otro bobard porque no
can't be more of an idiot that he doesn't know that
puede ser más idiota que no sabe que
when I say something I have the
cuando yo digo algo tengo la
WhatsApp conversation, I have a video, I
conversación de WhatsApp tengo video
have RAE you're crazy RAE the only one
tengo RAE tú estás loco RAE el único
here who has been in prison for committing
aquí que ha estado recluso por cometer
crimes is you okay you threatened to
delitos eres tú vale que amenazaste con
kill a man because because you never
matar a un hombre porque porque vete tú
know the money mess you have
a saber jaleo de dinero que te tienes
with him that you're always getting into
con él que siempre estás metidos en
financial trouble okay But the only one
fregados económicos vale Pero el único
who has spent a
que de momento ha pasado un fin de
weekend in jail so far and they'll probably
semana en la cárcel Y seguramente te
put you in Because look at how you are You're
meterán Porque fíjate tú como eres Eres
aggressive on the internet imagine in
agresivo en internet imagínate en la
life but if it's that in all the
vida pero si es que todas en todas las
arguments that he's said something he's
discusiones que que ha dicho algo ha
talked about hitting the other guy when he
hablado de pegarle al otro cuando
argued with Gibel when he argued with
discutió con gibel cuando discutió con
Dallas when he argued with Dallas he said I
Dallas cuando discutió con Dallas dijo
do it like this with my hand and I
yo lo hago así con la mano y lo y lo
put it to fly I don't know what I don't know how much you,
pongo a volar no sé qué no sé cuánto tú
this guy, you're a guy, like you are, from the
este tío eres un tío como eres de la
condition that you
condición que
are
eres
absolutely everything for me to tweet, you're not
absolutamente todo para yo twitear no
white and  black look memingo go
Tas blanco y negro Mira memingo anda a
suck his [ __ ] he's a failure continue wasting your
chupársela es fracasado sigue per tu
time with that failure here don't come
tiempo con ese fracasado aquí no vengas
because suddenly you can learn and
porque de repente puedes aprender y de
suddenly you earn money then go to
repente ganas plata entonces vete a
where the failure is that liar
donde el fracasado ese mentiroso
saying that oh oh putting on a show Oh
diciendo que oh oh haciendo un show Oh
how ra to say that jav oliveira talks
como ra a decir que jav oliveira habla
to 14 year old girls on discord said
con niñas de 14 años por discord dicho
by himself clown
por él mismo payaso
this no no r
esto no no
piece of clown it was 8 in the
r pedazo de payaso me dieron las 8 de la
morning clown until 8 in the morning
mañana payaso hasta las 8 de la mañana
this is the real sleepover the real sleepover
est es la pijamada real la pijamada real
the real sleepover better than seeing someone
la pijamada real mejor que ver a alguien
accusing another of being with minors I
que acusa a otro estar con menores yo
accuse someone of being with minors
acus a alguien de estar con menores
Where is Where is the accusation of
Dónde está Dónde está la acusación de
being with minors let's see where where where where is
estar con menores a ver dónde dónde
the accusation eh first of all
dónde dónde está la acusación eh primero
this tweet is fake obviously he's crazy eh
que este tweet es fake obv está loco eh
No he's not crazy he's
No no está loco está
crazy Look, well I'm not going to say what I
loco Mira yo bueno no voy a decir lo que
was going to say I'm not going to say what I was going to
iba a decir no voy a decir lo que iba a
say because there are lawsuits against the person
decir porque tiene hay demandas en en el
involved but everyone gets together with
involucrado pero cada uno se junta con
what they can get together no no
lo que con lo que se puede juntar no no
but he's crazy eh I mean he's crazy
pero está loco eh o sea está loco Es que
He doesn't even know  you don't understand Of course you
no sabe ni él no está entendiendo Claro
called me a pedophile ra he
que me has llamado pedófilo ra me ha
called me a pedophile to Dallas that you were
llamado pedófilo a mí al Dallas que te
hanging out with two
juntabas con él hace dos
months ago no I never had this and it doesn't matter
meses no esto nunca lo tié yo que da
that the tweet is fake
igual que el tweet sea fake
obviously the TT is a parody but
evidentemente el TT es una parodia pero
of what you said but of course
de lo que tú has dicho pero claro que lo
you said this ra Where is what does
has dicho tú esto ra Dónde está qué es
the T say first that est look they
lo que pone el T primero que est mira me
put me in jail because I went to
metieron en la cárcel porque fui a
report a man who
denunciar a un hombre que me que me
owed me money and the police made a mistake and
debía dinero y la policía se equivocó y
locked me up you say that [ __ ] You say that
me encerró a mí esa pendejada la dices
[ __ ] that they
tú Esa esa pendejada la dices tú que a
put you in jail for a
ti te han metido en la cárcel un fin de
weekend because the other guy owed you money
semana porque el otro te debía dinero a
trust you the nonsense you're
ti fíate tú la la payasada que tú
spouting How rude he is when he
sueltas Qué mala educación tiene al
speaks he's crazy he's crazy but if you have to
hablar es un loco está loco pero si ha
see it he's
que verlo que está
crazy tweet is fake obviously no I
loco tweet es fake obviamente no esto
never had this and You're applauding that's that
nunca lo té yo y Estás aplaudiendo eso
yes you applaud it no you piece of
es eso sí lo aplaudes no pedazo de
clown that you come here to say that
payaso que vienes para acá a decir que
how are they going to tell a lie you applaud this tweet
cómo van a decir mentira este tweet lo
so this tweet is
aplaudes entonces este tweet es
basadisimo and I'm going to retweet it
basadisimo y lo voy a retuitear ahora
right now Where is the
mismo Dónde está el
tweet no no all of us here right
tweet no no todos los que estamos aquí
now are going to retweet that tweet
ahora mismo vamos a retuitear ese tweet
Where is the tweet of the best tweet I've
Dónde está el tweet de los mejores tweet
posted this year eh Look at that
que he puesto en el año eh Mira qué
teteo [ __ ] these
teteo gilipo eses
eh where the [ __ ] is the TT Of the crazy one
eh dónde [__] está el TT Del loquito
Look at this you in jail Look at you in
Mira este tú en la cárcel Mira tú en la
jail okay they put me in jail
cárcel vale me metieron en la cárcel
because I went to report a man who
porque fui a denunciar un hombre que me
basadisimo
basadisimo
let's go one of the best [ __ ] tweets I've
vamos de los mejores [__] tet que he
posted this whole year what are you telling me
puesto en todo el año qué me estás
retweet step is failed marginal Ah You do
retweet paso es fracasado marginal Ah
applaud this no that Ja olira
Esto sí lo aplaudes no que Ja olira se
invents and edits a tweet of mine You do
invente y edite un tweet mío Esto sí lo
applaud this No but what I say that
aplaudes No pero lo que digo yo que sí
is true you do applaud that I mean you
es verdad eso sí lo aplaude o sea usted
applaud lies and refute truths
aplauden mentiras y rebaten verdades
Confessions of themselves I mean that t
Confesiones de ellos mismos o sea ese t
I wrote it as much as what your master
lo redacté yo tanto como lo que tu amo
says that I wrote for him about pambi I called it
dice que le redacté sobre pambi le puse
[ __ ] amorphous pathetic I call old Javi
[__] amorfo patético pongo al viejo Javi
oliveira go talk is the accusation
oliveira anda a hablar est la acusación
to the old man I'm younger than him go
al viejo soy más joven que él anda a
talk to girls at 14 on discord
hablar con niñas a 14 por discord
while your wife sleeps old wanker
mientras tu mujer duerme viejo [__] en
when did I lie Where is the
qué momento he mentido Dónde está la
lie Where where until what time did
mentira Dónde dónde hasta hasta qué hora
you stay Javi yesterday it was 8 in the
te quedaste Javi ayer dieron las 8 de la
morning 8 in the morning with the child
mañana 8 de la mañana con el niño
crying and partying with whom with whom with
llorando y festa con quién con quién con
whom can say it
quién lo puede decir
laita we have been a trio eh there was
laita estamos ha siendo un trío eh había
another Who was the
otra Quién era la
[Music]
[Música]
another is that they are idiots brother They are idiots they are
otra es que son imbéciles brother Son
idiots I mean they
imbéciles son imbéciles o sea ellos
want to refute things when I have
quieren rebatir las cosa cuando tengo
videos I have
videos tengo
conversations I have WhatsApp the same is
conversaciones tengo WhatsApp igual está
crazy what they are saying Hey
loco qué lo que están diciendo Epa tú
can you believe that this piece of failure
puedes creer que el pedazo de fracasado
or Taco this guy from the gubel says that
o Taco este del del gubel dice que
supposedly that what about that I went
supuestamente lo de que lo de que yo fui
to the police to report this guy who
a la policía a denunciar al tipo este
robbed me and that robbed me the guy
que me robó y que me robó el tipo lo
put him in jail eh Not the guy that's
metieron a él en la cárcel eh No al tipo
where the whole problem happened and
ahí fue que ocurrió todo el problema y
that it's a lie that what I did is true
que es mentira que es verdad lo que hice
Javi oliveira that it's true that I
Javi oliveira que es verdad que yo le
fell on him
caé [__] al
caser a kiss
caser un beso
Alex We would have to see what
Alex Habría que ver qué qué es lo que
happened for him with what they have him
pasó para que él con qué lo tienen
grabbed for him to change so much he is
agarrado para que él cambie tanto sea
such a pancake and change so much you have it in your
tan panqueque y cambie tanto tien
hand nra has it in hand with nothing He
agarrado nra tiene agarrado con nada
was simply a fake So he is
Sencillamente era un careta Entonces es
a fake interested in the moment of
un careta interesado en el momento de
fame When one hates him he hates him and
fama Cuando a uno lo odia lo odia y
when everyone loves another and loves him
cuando todo el mundo ama a otro y lo ama
exo Exactly a suck-up a beleta without
exo Exacto un chupamedias un beleta sin
personality Ah this to guibel based based
personalidad Ah esto al guibel basado
gubel you are he has no
basado gubel lo eres no tiene
personality or rather his personality is to
personalidad o sea su personalidad es
applaud him Oh yes Oh how based what are
que lo aplauda Ay sí Ay qué basado qué
the otacos going to say now that he
van a decir ahora los otacos que que
is based with the twit thing how am I
está basado con lo del twit que cómo yo
going to say that Ja oliveira talking on
voy a decir que Ja oliveira hablar por
discord with girls until morning what is he going to
discord con niñas hasta la mañana qué va
say who is the idiot him or me Who
a decir quién es el vasado él o yo Quién
is the idiot let's see idiot he is very
es el vasado a ver vasado está muy
idiot I said Lie it's the same Javi
vasado dije Mentira es el mismo Javi
oliveira saying it clown what are you going to
oliveira diciéndolo payaso qué vas a
say until what time Let's see let's
decir hasta qué hora A ver vamos a
remember until what time he stays
recordar hasta qué hora se queda
talking on discord with 13
hablando por discord con niñas de 13
year old girls until what time 8 in the morning
años hasta qué hora las 8 de la mañana
Ah  until 8 in the morning with who
Ah hasta las 8 de la mañana con quién
with who let's see Javi with who with who I
con quién a ver Javi con quién con quién
could say Laurita
pu decir Laurita
and But look you know what the otacus are going to do
y Pero mira sabes queé van a hacer los
no this [ __ ] guy is going to
otacus no el [__] mental este va a
come and say on Twitter any
venir y va a decir en Twitter cualquier
nonsense
barb
Christmas kisses
Navidad besos
Sasuke that he makes up and he's going to come
Sasuke que se invente y va a
out He's crazy he's crazy he's crazy he's crazy he's crazy he's
salir Está loco está loco está loco está
crazy
loco está loco
[Music]
[Música]
eh what a barbarity that he makes up he's crazy
eh barbaridad que se invente está loco
can you please send me an alert about this
me podéis hacer un una alerta de esto
and
y
leave Twitter whatever nonsense he
salir Twitter cualquier barbaridad que
makes up and
se invente y
leave suck me a kiss p other cco
salir me chupan un un beso p otros cco
members [ __ ] there are only five super
miembros [__] faltan solo cinco super
chats left will we arrive or I'll close the live
chat llegaremos o cierro el directo
early so I don't play the audio I'm going to
antes para no poneros el audio voy a
close the live to play the audio Ah I
cerrar directo para poneros el audio Ah
can't extend it
no puedo ampliarlo
whatever nonsense he makes up and they're
cualquier barbaridad que se invente y
going to come
van a
out based
salir basado
based whatever nonsense he
basado cualquier barbaridad que se
makes up and they're going to come
invente y van a
out bado bado could you send me an
salir bado bado me podía hacer una
alert about that please he's crazy what a jerk you
alerta de eso porfa está
[ __ ] guys but you
grillado os retrasados mentales pero
know that I like to deny the clown
sabes que me gusta desmentir al payaso
of the gubel who is a poor
del gubel que es un pobre payaso
failed clown a failed liar I mean it
fracasado un fracasado mentiroso o sea
's the same  of a liar that Javi Oliveira that's why he's
es igual de mentiroso que Javi oliveira
sucking Javi
por eso se la está chupando a Javi
Oliveira Because he's just as much of a liar and a
oliveira Porque es igual de mentiroso y
failure he's not sucking me off It's that he
fracasado no me la está chupando Es que
only says we want audio a kiss
solo solo dice queremos audio un beso
photos there are four missing there are four
fotos faltan cuatro faltan cuatro
kids that the gubel is not sucking me off
chavales que no me la está chupando el
nothing could be further from the truth I
gubel nada más lejos de la realidad o
mean what's happening is that you're
sea es que lo que pasa es que tú estás
crazy He only spouts nonsense I mean you
grillado Es que solo suelta tontería o
're not saying anything that makes
sea es que no estás diciendo nada con
sense You're crazy he
sentido Estás loco
wants to go sit and have coffee with
quiere ir a sentarse a tomar el café con
him That's right he's the ball this piece of
él Así es a la bola es este pedazo de
unhappy who wants to go have coffee
infeliz que quiere ir a tomarse un café
with the one who has called him everything I
con el que lo lo ha llamado de todo o
mean these people have no dignity
sea es que esta gente no tiene dignidad
these people just because of
esta gente por Solamente porque por
having people but you start
tener gente pero que tú te pones
talking to the
hablarte con el
delox but you start talking to the delox
delox pero que tú te pones a hablarte
and telling the delo And
con el delox y a decirle al delo Y a
who went to Ricky that he has a
quién fue al Ricky que que que tiene un
hitman The Dallas mik a kiss you
sicario El Dallas mik un beso te
made up that they had some hitmen
inventaste que tenían unos sicarios
disguised as
disfrazados de
rapid what the [ __ ] are you talking about dignity man you
rapid qué [__] hablas tú de dignidad tío
've been in jail for a
que has estado en la cárcel un fin de
weekend for God knows what  things what are you
semana por vete tú a saber qué cosas qué
going to talk about
vas a hablar tú de
dignity a kiss
dignidad un beso
Roy applauding him in a chat they are capable
Roy aplaudiendolo en un chat son capaz
of crawling do whatever whatever
de arrastrarse hacer lo que sea lo que
for fame whatever they are
sea por fama lo que sea son unos
crawling everything everyone everything how can't they
arrastrados todo todos todo como no
live off anything else They only
pueden vivir de otra cosa Solamente
live off this [ __ ] of getting money donated to them I
viven de esta [__] de que les donen
mean it's the reality of getting
plata O sea que es la realidad de que
money donated to them not like us who
les donen plata no como nosotros que
are the crypto who can who are the
somos los cript que podemos que somos
crypto bro
los crpto bro
eh a kiss Alex a kiss Salvador
eh un beso Alex un beso Salvador
51 51
51 51
it's I think it's time
es creo que es el momento de que
we put on that audio that I
pongamos ese audio que he
promised [ __ ] the kids have
prometido [__] la chavalería ha
achieved the 50 challenge for the first time
logrado por primera vez el reto de 50
[ __ ] for the first time the kids have achieved the 50 challenge
[__] por primera vez Ha logrado el reto
eh I'm going to put on the audio okay this is
eh voy a poner el audio vale esto es un
just a clip
clip solamente
Okay alanne but nobody's
Okay alanne pero si es que nadie lo
applauding says alanne has someone told
aplaude dice alanne alguien le ha dicho
this idiot that he's the best and he
al tontito este que es la [__] y se lo
believed it Poor thing nobody tells him he's the
ha creído Pobrecito nadie le dice que es
best but everybody
la [__] pero si es que todo el mundo
KNOWS that everybody is laughing at
SAE que se está todo el mundo riendo del
him all the time he
él todo el tiempo
's very
t es muy
stupid he's crazy
tonto es que está loco
eh  Okay Don't make noise okay
eh vale No hagáis ruido vale
this is an audio that belongs to a clip
esto es un audio que pertenece a un clip
Okay
Okay
Uh there are several scenes that are musical
Eh hay varias escenas que son musicales
And obviously people sing
Y evidentemente pues la gente canta la
people dance and stuff
gente baila y esas cosas
okay this is an audio that belongs to a
vale esto es un audio que pertenece a un
clip
clip
okay it's a
vale es una
girl named Nerea okay
chica que se llama nerea okay
p pamam p
p pamam p
[Music]
[Música]
by Nerea Ruis
par nerea ruis
Salor Nerea Ruis
salor nerea ruis
Salor okay I follow her on
salor vale Yo la sigo en
Instagram she does performances she's a
instagram hace actuaciones es un artista
super talented artist okay she does live shows on
s super talentosa vale hace directos en
Twitch
Twitch
and uploads videos to Instagram on Twitter too
e sube vídeos a Instagram en Twitter
okay I've known her for a long
también vale la conozco hace mucho
time Okay Well I asked her
tiempo Okay Bueno pues le le he pedido
one thing which was to sing this okay
una cosa que era que cantase esto vale
well the video is much better
bueno el vídeo es mucho mejor
obviously okay the video is much
evidentemente vale el vídeo es mucho
better okay but here you have the
mejor vale pero aquí tenéis el
audio here you have the audio of that video
audio aquí tenéis el audio de ese vídeo
which is its part okay then This
que es su parte vale luego Esto va
obviously goes with a video C with a
evidentemente con con un vídeo C con una
performance okay You'll see
actuación vale Ya lo veréis
[Music]
[Música]
aunt is crazy
tía es de loco
eh it's crazy
eh es de loco
eh And why haven't you seen the video
eh Y por qué no habéis visto el vídeo
eh And why are you not watching the video and
eh Y por no estáis viendo el vídeo y
well and well the performance
bueno y bueno la actuación
and the station
y la estación
eh No no no the video  You see
eh No no no el vídeo lo veis en el
the video in the rewind You see it in the rewind How
rewind el vídeo lo veis en el rewind Qué
beautifully she sings No no eh talent but it's
bonito canta no no eh talento pero es
because she made the base obviously
que ha hecho ella la base evidentemente
because if not the copy would jump out of course I
porque si no me salta el copy claro no
can't put the original song
puedo poner la canción original
logically she did it she did the
lógicamente lo ha hecho ella lo ha hecho
whole base the voice everything
ella todo la base la voz todo
eh
eh
buah Merry Christmas babe I hope
buah Feliz Navidad churrita Espero que
the new year brings you the best because
el año nuevo te traiga lo mejor pues
the year is coming strong eh Put a
viene fuerte el año eh Pon un
frame no no a frame no but apart from that it
frame que no no un frame no pero aparte
's not edited eh this clip is not
no está montado eh este clip no está
edited this clip goes with another person and
montado este clip va con otra persona y
it's a kind of video clip
es una especie de videoclip
No obviously I'm not the one
No evidentemente yo no soy el que lo
dancing it you'll see who dances it you
baila ya lo veréis quién lo baila que
all
todos lo
know it LoL I'm going to put it again I'm
conocéis LoL lo voy a poner otra vez lo
going to put it again I'm going to put it again I'm
voy a poner otra vez lo voy a poner otra
going to put it again
vez lo voy poner otra vez
[Music]
[Música]
n it's crazy eh it's crazy eh it's crazy
n es de loco eh es de loco eh es de loco
The talent that the girl has eh it
El Talento que tiene la chavala eh
's crazy The talent that the girl has
es de loco El Talento que tiene la
eh a kiss Laura You won't be Laurita
eh un beso Laura No serás Laurita
no a
no un
kiss the girl's name is Nerea Ruiz
beso la chica se llama nerea Ruiz
salor
salor
follow her because she is  that has a talent
seguirla porque es que tiene un talento
that's crazy man I mean, she was the
que lo flipas tío o sea era la era la
perfect chosen one for this shot eh, she was the
elegida perfecta para esta toma eh era
perfect chosen one
elegida perfecta
eh, she's a genius, she sings it all No, no, it
eh es una genia se lo canta todoa No no
's brutal
es es brutal
[Music]
[Música]
eh No, no, he dances to
eh No no lo baila al
a lot of cloth, a lot of cloth no, he doesn't dance to it,
mucha tela mucha tela no no lo baila lo
you know he's the girl's boyfriend, he's
conocéis que es el novio de la chica es
her partner that I've mentioned a lot is
su pareja que lo he mencionado much es
here eh that he also has a channel about
aquí eh que tiene un canal también de
video games and and so on and we have
videojuegos y y demás y lo hemos
mentioned it here because Of course you know that
mencionado aquí porque Claro sabéis que
I'm a big fan of Michael Jackson and and
soy muy fan de Michael Jackson y y
Alejandro Alex White Alex white Eh Well
Alejandro Alex White Alex blanco Eh Pues
I think he's the best that that that
yo creo que es el mejor que que que que
acts as Michael Jackson The truth is she
actúa de Michael Jackson La verdad ella
plays Ariana Grande eh she does
hace de de Ariana Grande eh ella hace
Ariana
actuaciones de Ariana
Grande performances but it's it's crazy eh it's crazy
Grande pero es es de loco eh es de loco
when she sent me the audio Well of course I
cuando me ha mandado el audio Pues claro
had the problem that I wanted to put it by
tenía el problema que quería poner por
eggs because it's that this is
huevos porque es que esto es
eem this has been very viral and the song
eem esto ha sido muy viral e la canción
the song is Old But it has been very
el tema es Antiguo Pero ha sido muy
viral this year with it with dipool but no, no, no,
viral este año con el con dipool pero no
Alex doesn't dance it, Alex doesn't
no lo baila Alex no lo baila Alex lo
dance it, someone that you all know and and
baila alguien que todos conocéis y y
well and she  he comes out singing obviously
bueno y ella sale cantando evidentemente
but it's no no no it's that it's cinema dude it's that it's
pero es no no no es que es cine tío es
cinema it's that cinema
cine es que cine
dipol dipol diple look let's suck it off let's
dipol dipol diple mir a chuparla vamos a
keep watching the crazy one no Hey Thanks
seguir viendo al loquito no Oye Gracias
for the challenge Thanks for the challenge eh thanks thanks
por el reto Gracias por el reto eh
for the challenge
gracias gracias por el reto
family What's up Cristian how are
familia Qué tal Cristian cómo
you doing do you need to be pulling
andas necesid estarle jalando bolas a
anyone's balls this one well it's your turn to crawl I mean when it's time to crawl bro it's time to
nadie este pues les toca arrastrarse o
crawl I wanna crawl crawl me
arrastrarse quier arrastrarse arrástreme
Where's the lie you piece of
Dónde está la mentira pedazo de
[ __ ] you piece of [ __ ] I mean it's that they're so
fracasado pedazo de fracasado o sea es
pathetic These guys are so pathetic this gubel is so but so but so but
dan tanta pena este gubel es tan pero
so pathetic everything he
tan pero tan pero tan penoso todo lo que
says he throws it all away that he's
dice se las se las tira de que de que es
funny no that literal out of stupidity PR to
cómico no que literal por tontería PR
scare the Twitter accounts that come
estigar las cuentas de Twitter que dar
against Javi Look I'll tell you something this guy
contra Javi Mira te digo algo este tipo
is just as false he's just as false
es igual de falso es igual de falso
just as false here that pape Oh I'll pape you Where is
igual de falso acá que pape Ay te papear
the marginal double chin Where where is
Dónde está la papada marginal Dónde
the papea where Who pape
dónde está la papea dónde Quién papea
who pape you only you Ray but it's
quién te papea solo tú Ray pero es que
not even papeado it's that ...
no es ni papeado es que hace el ridículo
a crazy man
es que está completamente como un loco
eh I mean that's how a crazy man sees eh that's how
eh o sea es como ve un loco eh es como
a crazy man sees eh screaming alone
ve un loco eh gritando solo
eh it's that who pape who I'm here
eh es que quién pape a quién yo aquí
saying go to Javi Olivera go
estoy diciendo anda a Javi Olivera anda
talk to a 14 year old girl on discord
a hablar con niña de 14 años por discord
while your wife sleeps and here he is
mientras tu mujer duerme y aquí está
saying it himself
diciéndolo él mismo no está está
he is not he is saying it himself these are not my words these
diciendo él mismo no son mis palabras
are his words a meme has come out
son las palabras de él ya salió una meme
flork you're really [ __ ] me you must
flork de verdad me estás jodiendo me
be [ __ ] me you must
tienes que estar jodiendo me tienes que
be [ __ ] me Ah no no no no no no no no
estar jodiendo Ah no no no no no no no
no you had a great time kihar But where where No no no no no
no la pasaste kihar Pero a dónde a dónde
no Please tell me it's a
No no no no no no Por favor díganme que
lie tell me it's a lie
es mentira díganme que es mentira la
people bought I got rich and delicious
gente compró me saqué ricas y deliciosas
x I mean it filled the bonding no I can't
x o sea llenó el bonding no No puedo
believe it I can't believe it that it filled the
creerlo No puedo creerlo que llenó el
bonding it filled the bonding [ __ ] it filled
bonding llenó el bonding cabrones llenó
no the bonding it took 5 seconds yeah Well I mean
no el bonding 5 segundos tardó sí Bueno
you don't believe it either no obviously
o sea tampoco te la creas no obviamente
manipulation well brutal don't believe it Do
manipulación bueno brutal no te la creas
n't believe it either
Tampoco no te la creas tampoco A ver
Let's see let's see it in de
vamos a verla vamos a verla en de
screener  Let's go see her in de
screener Mejor vamos a verla en de
scener And now they've already sent her to the guano
scener Y ya y ya la mandaron al guano
let's see how much liquidity she has let's
vamos a ver cuántas liquides tiene vamos
see how much liquidity she has they paid her
a ver cuántas liquides tiene le pagaron
the Boost Epa they paid her the Boost of 500
el Boost Epa le pagaron el Boost de 500
and everything Epa How based That is based on
y todo Epa Qué basado Ese sí es basado
tennis sa How to knock people down
el tenis sa Cómo cómo tumbar a la gente
Epa well 96,000 in liquids is not
Epa bueno 96,000 de liques no está para
bad at all I thought it was going to be worse
nada mal pensé que le iba a ir peor
I thought it was going to be worse To be
pensé que le iba a ir peor Para serte
honest no I mean eh I mean really it
honesto no O sea eh o sea de verdad me
seems to me that it seems to me that no it's not bad
parece que me parece que no no tiene mal
performance now let's see the holders
desempeño ahora vamos a ver los holders
because it's worrying me the top traders
porque preocupante yo los top traders
too Look Marshall this one let's
también Mira Marshall este vamos a vamos
give about 600,000 seconds to this
a darle un unos 600,000 segundos al
Marshall who comes here because
Marshall este que viene aquí a que
we are here waiting to
nosotros estamos aquí pendientes de de
make money go and suck guibel go
hacer plata vaya y chupes al guibel vaya
kneel down
arrodíllate
badly your balls you [ __ ] liar go go
mal las bolas un [__] mentiroso vaya
if he doesn't do it if he doesn't do it the
vaya si no lo hace si no lo hace los
moderators will do it myself come on
moderadores lo hago yo mismo vamos aale
Time out this SAP [ __ ] shitty idiot
Time out este SAP [__] imbécil de [__]
out here long out nobody cares
fuera aquí largo out a nadie le importa
what you think a  nobody cares i do
lo que pienses tú a nadie le interesa a
n't care what you think you got
mí no me interesa lo que piens te
fooled you got fooled you [ __ ] shitty failures
paparon te paparon [__] fracasados de
all of you have no life they live
[__] todos no tienen vida viven
sucking off a lying [ __ ] Not an
chupándosela a un [__] mentiroso Ni
idiot who still lives with his mom, I
idiota que vive con la mamá todavía o
mean That's the example to follow of people
sea Ese es el ejemplo a seguir de gente
living with their mom until they're
vivir con la mamá hasta los
30 what do we see now places for me another
30 qué vemos ahora lugares porme otro
crazy please pme another crazy
loco porfa pme otro loco
places to trust this character
lugares para fiarte de este personaje
man the character is looking good
hombre el personaje apunta manera tesa
the character is looking good
el personaje apunta maneras
no Give me give me something not the
no Ponme ponme algo no
Pambi thing let's see the Pambi thing let's
lo de pambi vamos a ver lo de pambi a
see the community How are you in the
ver la comunidad Cómo estáis en la
community Look look look look look look
comunidad Mira mira mira mira mira mira
eh the day Javi's rewind comes out
eh el día que salga el rewind de Javi yo
when grandpa finally goes bald I'm
cuando el abuelo por fin se quede calvo
never going to go bald Javi
no me voy a quedar calvo nunca Javi la
saw it coming you go ask me Hey they
vio venir tú me vayas preguntando Oye
're giving us too many members for
nos están dando muchísimos miembros para
me there's none that are
m no hay ninguno
very happy eh Ah no no no no no no no no no do
de contento muy fácil eh Ah no no no no
n't say those things it's just that if you want
no no digas esas cosas es que si quieres
some members it's chame Eh yes Look 50
algún miembro es chame Eh sí Mira 50
members but Loli has given away 50
miembros pero que Loli ha regalado 50
members you go Loli Loli  gave away 50
miembros tú me vayas Loli Loli regaló 50
members there eh a little self-esteem a
miembros ahí eh un poco de autoestima un
little self-esteem You know I always
poco de autoestima Tú sabes que siempre
have room for you in the agenda I
tengo hueco para ti en la agenda lo
tell you the same and be careful because today they're
mismo te digo y y cuidadito que hoy te
going to take away the members one [ __ ]
van a sacar el de los miembros [__] de
member I want one of course It's that I see
miembro yo quiero uno claro Es que veo
50 members I say How many members I
50 miembros digo Cuántos miembros Yo
want but no but I wanted that no that I
quiero pero no pero yo quería que no que
wanted a member of I say I wanted but I do
quería un miembro de digo yo quería pero
n't know how to do it because suddenly I see
no sé cómo se hace porque de repente veo
a member two three everyone member member member
un miembro dos tres todo el mundo
I say [ __ ]
miembro miembro miembro digo [__]
How many members [ __ ] How weird it sounds what a little word they
Cuántos miembros [__] Qué raro suena
put
vaya palabrita que le han puesto lo de
member eh You have to not warn me of
miembro eh Tienes que no me avisa de de
the members does not
los miembros no me
warn me What a good time to look at this
avisa Qué buen momento para mirar este
big face face Javi the cani no dude 4
cara cara grande Javi el cani no tío 4
hours eh Ah no three
horas eh Ah no tres
three no no no no no nobody dumb enough to
tres no no no no no nadie tan tonto para
eat you for Ah Ugh
comerte para Ah Uf
[ __ ] this is photop legs This video
cabrones esto es fotop patas Este vídeo
was uploaded by
ha subió el
Dallas this is photop legs of
Dallas esto es fotop patas de princesa
Disney princess what the [ __ ] is
Disney qué [__] es
this what the [ __ ]
esto qué [__]
RAE from an area of ​​Venezuela
RAE desde una zona de Venezuela en la
where they use a lot of profanities to converse
que usan muchas groserías para conversar
normally that's why their
normalmente por eso sus formas
incorrect forms But from there to the end of  what
incorrectas Pero de allá al fin de qué
area is the mental hospital Well, you
zona es del manicomio
're very happy, no I mean, you're
No pues estáis muy happy no O sea estáis
very comfortable Look, look, look at
muy a gustito Mira mira mira las fotitos
my pictures from yesterday, eh
mías de ayer eh
Look at my pictures from yesterday, eh The Dallas grandma
Mira las fotitos mía de ayer eh Me me
sent me an audio when the live was starting, she's to
mandó un audio cuando estaba empezando
die for eh I mean, how charming she is, she
para comérsela eh O sea qué encantadora
sends me an audio to tell me how
es me manda un audio para decirme lo
handsome we were here and what a
guapo que estábamos aquí y qué tipito
cute body Lorena has, literally the audio
tan lindo tiene Lorena literal el audio
eh One day I have to invite her
eh Un día la tengo que invitar
eh One day I have to invite her Eh yes yes
eh Un día la tengo que invitar Eh sí sí
yes she's a delight
sí es un encanto
God God my favorite is I think
God God mi favorita es Es que creo que
this is the best Well, this one and this one isn't this one
es esta la mejor bueno esta y esta no
This photo is God eh This photo is
esta esta esta foto es God eh Esta foto
God What the
God Qué
[ __ ], what the [ __ ] is this,
[__] qué [__] es esto
man
tío
[Music]
[Música]
Christmas Merry Christmas, prosperous new year and
Navidad Feliz Navidad prospero año y
happiness, happy
felicidad feliz
Christmas Merry
Navidad Feliz
Christmas without spam Congratulate me, you're my
navidad sin spam Felicítame eres mi
idol, I already have 100 subscribers, face
ídolo ya tengo 100 suscriptores cara
crying loudly The truth is that I do
llorando fuerte Es que la verdad es que
n't care, man, and without spam, how sincere
no me importa tío y sin spam qué sincero
Eh then
Eh entonces
troman says that everything is bite Why is it
troman dice que todo er bite Por qué es
like an insult to delos and to  raed
como un insulto para delos y para raed
[Music]
[Música]
in Dallas writing in the
em Dallas escribiendo en la
salsería Hey but Dallas writing
salsería Oye pero el Dallas escribiendo
in the salsería
en la salsería
look Dallas is a member of the salsería let's
mira el Dallas es miembro de la salsería
see eh Can you tell if he's a
ver eh Se puede saber si es
member he says this obsession of r to
miembro dice esta obsesión de r por
harm each project of is that he's
perjudicar cada proyecto de es que está
crazy but why For r and for delox it's
loco pero por qué Para r y para delox es
like some kind of insult the
como una especie de insulto lo de los
threesome thing kids 100% no
tríos chavalería 100% no
this is normal
esto es normal
dude this is
tío esto es
normal and this yes I was
normal y ya esto sí lo estuve
seeing it
viendo
Ah sure sure sure Yes it's because if not I
Ah claro claro claro Sí es porque si no
couldn't respond to the tweet
no podría responder al tweet
clear Dallas eh full kid eh
claro el Dallas eh full chaval eh le
can we give him
podemos dar
moderator so the sick harassers
moderador que los acosadores enfermitos
try to humiliate saying that I do
intenten humillar diciendo que me hago
threesomes with my girlfriend it's like making fun of it's
tríos con mi novia es como para burlarse
like making fun of a millionaire for
es como burlarse de un millonario por
having a yacht I just don't understand What is it you
tener yate Es que no entiendo Cuál es la
know what is it is that delos and
sabes cuál es la es que el delos y el
delos and the crazy eh del ra I mean they are like
delos y el loquito eh del ra o sea están
like messing with Dallas
como como metiéndose con el Dallas
because he does
porque hace
threesomes well This is what we have
tríos bueno Esto es lo que hemos
commented before Don't look at what
comentado antes No fíjate tú lo que se
delos invented  the other day the [ __ ]
inventó el delos el otro día la la [__]
joke And what about 2000 little people who
payasada Y qué hay 2000 personitas que
have liked this man even to
le han dado like a este hombre todavía a
this day even to
hoy todavía a día de
this day last week I met with the ceo
hoy la semana pasada me reuní con el ceo
of bitmark and I took the opportunity to explain what
de bitmark y aproveché para exponerle lo
happened with pambi delox at the
ocurrido con pambi delox en la
bakery I just thought about it I just
panadería ya justo lo he pensado justo
thought about it I just
lo he pensado justo lo he
thought about it
pensado
to Anne but I can't
al Anne pero no lo puedo
say it javiel peluca after a 2024 full
decir javiel peluca tras un 2024 lleno
of betrayals and malicious whales
de traiciones y ballenas maliciosas
Dallas brings us this Christmas the
Dallas nos trae esta Navidad la
resurrection of pambi 1 but without raes or
resurrección de pambi 1 pero sin raes ni
Javi oliveira taking 10k No way
Javi oliveira llevándose 10k No que va
no way I'm not going to take 10k but
no que va no me voy a llevar yo 10k pero
of course I'm going to take them I already have
claro que me los voy a llevar ya tengo
a few panis just in case what
yo unas cuantas de panis por si lo que
might
pueda
happen almost 300,000 impressions and only 2k
pasar casi 300.000 impresiones y solo 2k
likes rar one rar one rar one I'm
de like rar uno rar uno rar uno estoy
sure that this time he will reach the
seguro de que esta vez sí llegará a la
moon no no no without me no Ray has a
luna no no no sin mí no Ray tiene un
ton of B1 bread that he never sold to
montón de pan B1 que nunca le vendió a
these idiots who  come in that I
estos imbéciles que le metan que los
'm waiting for you to dump the losos how
estoy esperando para dumpear losos como
is it so Javier peluca you haven't given a thing
es así que Javier peluca no has dado una
eh Javier peluca you haven't given a thing
eh Javier peluca no has dado una
eh now he comes out with that it was look that I
eh ahora sale con que era mira que lo
Listen that I still have panis to
Listen que todavía tengo panis para
sell them in the [ __ ] face and they don't
venderles en la putísima caraa y no
know where I have them so they're
saben dónde los tengo así que están
fried and says Nitro now comes out with Kon
fritos y dice Nitro ahora sale con Kon
bite so that r would sell and that the reason
bite para que r vendiera y que la razón
or that they already support raed
o sea ya apoyan a raed
okay Now Nitro supports raed according to or that it
vale Ya Nitro apoya a raed según o sea
seems fine to him that raed well anyway and
le parece bien que raed bueno en fin y
that he doesn't doubt when he least wants it I
que no dude cuando menos se lo esere le
sell it to his face just like I rusp I fight
vendo en la cara así como me rusp puleo
with the scammer from Telegram Money and him and
con el scammer de Telegram Money y el y
the
el
wajiro the same one is going to get eaten doubled he doesn't
wajiro la misma se va a comer doblada no
know how many tokens I have I'm going to
sabe cuántos token tengo le voy a
burst that graph
reventar esa gráfica
and says Nitro It seems perfect to me this time they
y dice Nitro Me parece perfecto esta vez
deserve it well and the previous ones too
merecen bueno y las anteriores también
Ah okay okay okay okay they deserve it
Ah vale vale vale vale que se lo merecen
okay look at Red talking to delox
vale mira el Red hablándose con delox
my mother my mother I learned this
madre mía madre mía esto lo aprendí yo
in the sanctuary eh I mean the capí varas
en el santuario eh o sea las capí varas
are spread with the capí baras the cows
se untan con las capí baras las vacas
with the cows of
con las vacas
course but let's see if delox says that
la Claro pero a ver si delox dice que
pambi 1 is a scam
pambi 1 es una estafa
r is on the side not of
r está de parte no de
delox and r was part of pambi
delox y r era parte de pambi
too and has this where it is r
también y tiene esto dónde lo o sea r
just confirmed that he has a
acaba de confirmar que tiene una cartera
hidden wallet r just confirmed that he has a
escondida r acaba de confirmar que tiene
hidden wallet you can't have a wallet r you
escondida no puedes tener una cartera r
were part of the
eras parte del
iq 500 project
proyecto 500 de iq
no no [ __ ] around
no no jodas
How is he going to recognize That
Cómo va a reconocer
javiel said he didn't have a token let's see
Eso javiel dijo que no tenía token a ver
Román send me when he said that
Román Mándame cuando dijo
Román send me what he said when he
eso Román mándame eso que dijo cuando
said that he didn't have another
dijo que él no tenía otra cartera
hidden wallet and now he's saying that if he
escondida y ahora está diciendo que si
has a
tiene una cartera
hidden wallet tomorrow they'll show you the clip about
escondida mañana te sacan el clip sobre
taking a euro bill from pambi Well let's
llevarte billete de euro de pambi Pues a
see if it's true that I ever take
ver si es verdad que me llevo alguna vez
something son because a
algo hijo porque un
Bajío that I have a Bajío didn't give me
Bajío que tengo un Bajío no me regaló
some tokens a friend gave me
una amiga unos token me regaló una amiga
some tokens the other
unos token el otro
day for whatever might
día por lo que pueda
happen hidden with a holde
pasar escondid con un holde
Apparently big from pambi but but it
Aparentemente grande de pambi pero pero
's very strong
es muy fuerte
noo before give the review saying that the
noo antes da la review diciendo que el
problem with pambi is that people don't
problema de pambi es que que la gente no
holde  with balls By the way, since you're bringing
holde con [__] Por cierto ya que
up the subject, p, they've delisted it, they've
sacáis el tema p lo han deslistado lo
delisted bitmart
han deslistado bitmart
guys, since you're bringing up the subject of pambi and I had the tab open,
chavales ya que sacáis el tema de pambi
since you're bringing up the
y tenía la pestaña abierta ya que sacáis
subject of p Look, change tabs in
el tema de p Mira cambia de pestaña en
the browser and I had the tab
el navegador y la tenía la pestaña
open since you're bringing up the subject of p
abierta ya que sacáis el tema de pambi
My God
Dios mío
delox, it's not because of me anymore, it's because of
delox ya no es por mí ya es por
you, look at it, churra Maybe you can
ti mírelo churra A lo mejor lo puedes
still solve it,
solucionar todavía
eh, they've delisted it, they've delisted
eh lo han deslistado lo han deslistado
bitmart guys, do you remember that I had
bitmart chavales os acordáis que había
spoken with the ceo of bitmart and his
hablado con el ceo de bitmart y con su
assistant? Well, they've already kicked him out, they've already
asistente Bueno pues ya lo han echado ya
kicked here but you can't be
han echado aquí a pero no se puede ser
such a
tan
clown and me, but you can't be such a
payaso y yo pero no se puede ser tan
clown, do you remember that I spoke with the seo
payaso os acordáis que hablé con el seo
and with the assistant with the dosas from
y con el asistente con los dosas de
bitmar and they threw out pambi escam this
bitmar y han echado pambi escam este
fraudulent person and nothing, well, one
fraudulento y nada pues un problema
less problem now it's true that daras
menos ahora sí que es verdad que daras
is telling, well, the little lies, no,
está diciendo pues lasp mentirijillas no
that they haven't listed me because they have
que no me han listado por me han
delisted me for another reason, did
deslistado por otro motivo ha pasado
this happen guys  no Dallas no, I'm not
esto chicos no Dallas no es que lo estoy
saying it Dallas has taken a
diciendo Dallas ha sacado una captura de
screenshot where it says they are
pantalla donde pone que lo están
delisting it because they had no
deslistado porque no tenía
liquidity who told us that they were going to
liquidez quién nos avisó de que iban a
delist Pambi because I was talking
deslistar pambi porque estaba hablando
to the Pambi team telling them about the
con el equipo de pambi comentándoles El
problem that had been in the
problema que había habido en la
Spanish-speaking community about Pambi
comunidad hispana hablante sobre pambi
Tito dex then damn what a cringe
el Tito dex entonces ostia qué cringe
man what a
tío qué
cringe what a cringe What a
cringe qué cringe
coincidence that they just slip you and
Qué casualidad que justo te deslizan y
now you just look look what a coincidence
ahora tú justo mira mira qué casualidad
Look I'm going What a coincidence that just
Mira vo voy Qué casualidad que justo
now just now that Tito delox look he's
ahora justo ahora que el Tito delox mira
had time eh pambi has been without
que ha tenido tiempo eh pambi lleva sin
volume and without liquidity and made a
volumen y y sin liquidez y hecho una
mess at Bitmart for a long time
[__] en bitmart un montón de tiempo
but just now that Delox has had to see
pero justo ahora que delox tiene a ver
a long
un montón de
time the currency no it hasn't existed for a
tiempo la moneda no no existe hace un
long time opportunity to talk
montón de tiempo oportunidad de hablar
to the team talk to the CEO
con el equipo hablar con el propio ceo
of Bitmart himself and tell him the problem face to
de de bitmart y comentarle el problema
face just now that they unlist it
de cara justo ahora que lo deslan de
after I speak with them and they
después de que hable yo con ellos y me
tell me that they are going to delist it that I have it in
digan que lo van a deslistar que lo
writing suddenly Ah no no no no
tengo por escrito de repente Ah no no no
it's not because of a problem of  liquidity nothing
no es por un problema de liquidez nada
to do with delox please will you give or mean do
que ver con delox por favor darás o seaa
n't take this much from me either this
tampoco me quites este tanto que este
much is mine recognize recognize that I have
tanto es mío reconoce reconoce que te he
played my cards well and well what
jugado bien las cartas y pues lo que
happens well what you have if you scam and I
pasa pues lo que tien si tú estafas y yo
have contacts I go to the guy and I say You
tengo contactos voy al tío y le digo Tú
Excuse me I think you have listed a
Perdona que creo que has listado una
scam and he [ __ ] don't [ __ ] with me
estafa y él [__] que no me jodas en
seriously come out so much Yes yes yes Look look Yes
serio salido tanto Sí sí sí Mira mira Sí
in fact notice that in fact already at the
de hecho fíjate tú que de hecho ya en su
time the bitm do you remember that she put
momento la bitm os acordáis que ponía
tweet about pambi every time these
tweet sobre pambi cada vez que esta
people started to say that those of bmar
gente se ponían a decir que los de bmar
were against pambi I don't know what
estaban en contra de pambi no sé qué
But what talk how embarrassing this eh
Pero qué charla qué vergüenza esto eh
what a charlatan but what need eh to
qué charlatán pero qué necesidad eh de
invent these things too no he
inventarse ya también estas cosas no el
deleted my channel because I don't like
borro mi canal porque ya no me gustan
the thumbnails anymore damn I'm going to remove it I'm
las miniaturas ostia lo voy a quitar lo
going to remove it because I don't want problems and they
voy a quitar que no quiero problemas y
remove it So please all of this
lo quitan Entonces por favor todo esto
are scams no all of this here are
son estafas no todo esto de aquí son
scams no
estafas no
that then I see here everyone lying
que luego veo aquí a cada uno mintiendo
saying No no now we're going to list it I do
diciendo No no ahora lo vamos a listar
n't know where And this and that and start over
no sé dónde Y esto y lo otro y vuelve a
and  Please guys, don't fall for
empezar y por favor chicos no caigáis en
these scams because then you lose money and they screw
estas estafas que luego perdéis dinero y
you over. And Nitro already said this. It
os la lían y esto ya lo decía Nitro que
seems that what Dallas has been doing
se ve que lo que ha estado haciendo
now is with some wallets that they
Dallas Ahora es con unas wallets que ya
have already located, in case you haven't
tiene localizadas por por si no se ha
noticed, they have been buying Pambi at
dado cuenta han estado comprando pambi a
ridiculous prices. Well, let's
precios de risa porque Bueno vamos a
see in the screener how the great
verlo en de screener cómo está el gran
project is doing, the great currency. No, what currency
proyecto la gran moneda No qué moneda
did Dallas make? Well, the question is
hizo Dallas Bueno pues la pregunta es
which one. No, what currency have they made that isn't
cuál No qué moneda haya hecho que no sea
a scam, no, that would be the
un scam no esa sería la pregunta
correct question. But well, let's look, eh,
correcta Pero bueno vamos a mirar eh
Pambi. Let's see, it's here. I don't know if they're going to
pambi A ver est aquí no no sé si la van
change it from RET or what the hell are they going to
a cambiar de ret o qué pollas van a
do, but look. See, now they've pamped it, they've
hacer pero mira Ves Ahora la han pampe
pamped it, they're buying with
ellos la han pampe ellos comprando con
wallets, uh, with
wallets eh con wallets
secondary wallets, wallets that they think we don't
eh secundarias wallets que creen que no
know. Obviously, if
sabemos Cuáles son Obviamente si las
we have them located, and Well, here you can
tenemos localizadas y Bueno aquí podéis
see. Look, here you can see that the project
ver Mira aquí podéis ver que el proyecto
literally went to zero, I mean, to
se fue literalmente a cero O sea a cero
absolute zero, and now recently, if we
absoluto y ahora recientemente si nos
zoom in, I'm going to put it in logarithmic
acercamos voy a poner en logarítmico
so that it can be seen a little better. Now,
para que se vea un pelín mejor ahora
recently, it had a
recientemente Tuvo una subida
significant rise.  It's still absolutely in
significativa sigue absolutamente en la
[ __ ], I mean if you look
[__] es decir si tú te pones a mirar
from the
desde
highs to here it's still in minus
máximos hasta aquí sigue en un menos
man here at least at the moment
hombre aquí por lo menos en el momento
in which delos is looking at this I don't know
en el que delos está mirando esto no sé
what it will be. Now it has 90 it has
cómo será Ahora tiene un 90 tiene
0,000 of liquidity which according to raed is not
0.000 de liquidez que eso según raed no
bad at all. According to raed what he said about another token
mal según raed ha dicho sobre otro token
now it was not bad at all I don't know if it will be a
ahora no estaba nada mal no sé si será
lot or a
mucho o
little
poco
39.36 I mean
39,36 es decir está absolutamente
the project is absolutely devastated there is no way to
devastado el proyecto no hay por dónde
lift it but of course it was in
levantarlo pero claro es que estaba en
a 99 men with eh with 93 you know it was in
un men 99 con eh con 93 sabes estaba en
absolute [ __ ] it had been
absoluta [__] había quedado
completely disintegrated and now it
completamente desintegrado y ahora pues
's disintegrated eh point minus okay And
está desintegrado eh punto menos vale Y
what happened is that this candle here is
qué ha pasado que este velón de aquí es
a candle that although it is still at -99 it has gone
un velón que aunque siga en un -99 ha
up as you can see a by nu9 it is worth
subido como podéis ver un por nu9 vale
800 even reaching some
un 800 por incluso llegando a algún
point here we can see wait a moment
punto aquí podemos ver espera un momento
the maximum even reaching 1% a by
el máximo llegando incluso al 1% un por
14 because eh he has bought with
14 porque eh ha comprado con wallets
new wallets okay with it says here Look in fact
nuevas vale con dice aquí Mira de hecho
we have Nitro in the chat says Daniel
tenemos a Nitro en el chat dice Daniel
José The Legend  I'm not going to read this, man
José La Leyenda no voy a leer esto tío
Nitro You're a piece of troll eh Nitro
Nitro Eres un pedazo de troll eh Nitro
makes a curious presentation about
hace una presentación curiosa sobre
Dallas and says obviously he
sobre Dallas y dice obviamente ha
bought with new wallets half of
comprado con wallets nuevas la mitad de
the increase was caused by himself
la subida la ha provocado el solito
Well there you have it No yes he says he's
Bueno pues ahí lo tenéis No sí dice que
going to list it on m exchange Well be
lo va a listar en m exchange Bueno pues
careful I don't make calls inform the
cuidado no hago llamadas informe a los
exchanges What's going on because of course be
exchange De qué está pasando porque
careful I don't make calls
claro cuidado no hago llamadas
man How geeky is there an exchange that when
tío Qué friky hay exchange que cuando
they get a turkey with 12 million
les viene un pavo con 12 millones de
subscribers Even though half of them are Bots
suscriptores Aunque la mitad sean Bots
[ __ ] Well they say How crazy that I have to
[__] Pues dicen Qué locura que tengo
list this Oh and you also pay me
que listar esto Ah que además me pagas
great money you know I mean yeah
dinero estupendo sabes es decir si
no problem So it's normal that
ningún problema Entonces es normal que
he can get that [ __ ] to Listen to
él pueda conseguir que Listen esa [__]
anywhere practically that they don't
en cualquier sitio prácticamente que no
have dude like Listen to it on
tengan tío como lo Listen en el
bitmark like Listen to it on bitmark again
bitmark como lo Listen en bitmark otra
what is he going to
qué va a
say but of course still if they don't list it
decir pero claro todavía si no lo listan
on
en
bitmark it doesn't matter to him Not his thing but if they
bitmark le vale No su rollo pero si lo
list it next week on bitmark
listan la semana que viene en bitmark
what is he going to say well of course he is
qué va a decir pues claro él está
saying that he has spoken with the seo and that
diciendo que ha hablado con el seo y que
the seo has unlisted him because delos
el seo lo ha deslistado porque el delos
has told him that this is a
le ha dicho que esto es una
scam quietly  like with Serene
estafa calladito como con lo de serene
with Serene with the
con lo serene con lo de la orden de
restraining order with Ricky's complaint
alejamiento con lo de la denuncia de
with everything no with everything no with the
Ricky con todo no con todo no con los
hitmen No no he hasn't come back I haven't backed
sicarios No no ha vuelto no he vuelto a
down with the hitmen no it
recular con lo de los sicarios no que
was an invention of raet but man of course
fue un invento de raet pero hombre claro
there we will have to ask no I mean yes yes
ahí ya le Tendremos que preguntar no O
next week they list it
sea si si la semana que viene lo listan
on Bitmar this one there we will have to tell
en el bitmar este ahí habrá que decirle
Delox that you told us no that you
delox que tú nos has dicho no que tú nos
told us that you had spoken with the
has dicho que habías hablado con el
SEO seriousness okay I mean he is not going to
seo seriedad vale es decir no lo va a
list it on Binance because aans are
listar en un binance porque aans son
big words there go first
palabras mayores ahí van scams de primer
level scams okay here a second level scam is
nivel vale aquí un scam de segundo nivel
not going to enter but eh wow that
no va a entrar pero eh ostras que lo
Listen to it on a Mext on a Gate.io on a I
Listen en un mext en un gate.io en un yo
know you know on a cuin in things of this
que sé sabes en un cuin en cosas de este
style yes I can come to believe it
estilo sí me lo puedo llegar a creer por
why because in the end the team that is
qué porque al final el equipo que hay
there They know that a large part of their
ahí Ellos saben que gran parte de su
volume comes from enlistment of
volumen viene de alistamiento de
Allcoins they say damn that a
allcoins dicen [__] que ha venido un
kid came who says he has I don't know how many
chaval que dice que tiene no sé cuántos
million Followers and that  it has a
millones de Seguidores y que tiene una
currency and a community and this and that And he
moneda y una comunidad y esto y lo otro
says Well I'm coming forward Do you think it's
Y dice Bueno vengo adelante Tú crees que
a question of looking at Twitter or seeing
sea una poner a mirar Twitter o a mirar
if Delox said or if Nitro Launcher
si delox dijo o si Nitro Launcher
demonstrated or if Pepito commented no no no you don't
demostró o si Pepito comentó no no no no
know Yes well as Nitro says eh Dallas
sabes Sí bueno como dice Nitro eh Dallas
says that Mext is tier 1, that is, Mext will be
dice que mext es tier 1 o sea mext será
tier 1 in Guatemala and Chile you know but in
tier 1 en Guatemala y chile sabes per en
the real world Mext is a
el mundo real mext es un exchange de
second-rate exchange that doesn't matter it's an exchange that
segunda que no pasa nada es un exchange
I have used to buy some
que yo he utilizado para comprar alguna
currencies a very low bar when it comes to
moneda un listón muy bajo a la hora de
what they list And that they don't list and that They
qué listan Y que no listan y que
simply serve so that people who
Sencillamente sirven para que gente que
have projects Can list them
tiene proyectos Pues los pueda listar
there and have centralized liquidity and
ahí y tengan una liquidez centralizada y
access To facilities that are
acceso Pues a unas facilidades que en en
not available in the decentralized sector and that's it
el sector descentralizado no está y ya
but it's not I mean let's not
está pero que no es me explico que no
go here and say no no that they just
vayamos aquí a decir no no que acaban de
listed eh Pepito Coin on Binance you know like there are like
listar eh Pepito Coin en binance sabes
two very
en plan hay como como dos mundos muy
different worlds comparing Mext with Binance
diferentes comparar mexc con con binance
plus it's something that anyone
además es que es una cosa que cualquiera
can do not only by authority
puede hacer ya no solo por autoridad
but it is  that you go here to exchange
sino es que tú te vas aquí a exchange
ok derivatives same and you look look at
vale derivados mismamente y tú miras
the volume and you see that binance
miras el volumen y tú ves que binance
is right now with a mega
está ahora mismo con un volumen mega
high volume look it has 24,000 million it has
alto fíjate tiene 24,000 millones tiene
a high volume because it mainly
un volumen alto porque principalmente
works with a lot of alternative currencies
trabaja muchísimas monedas alternativas
it is an exchange in which I to buy
es un exchange en el que yo para comprar
according to what things I work there I have
según Qué cosas trabajo ahí no tengo
no problem I have an account in mext
ningún problema yo tengo cuenta en mext
but oops is to say that this is a
pero ostras es que decir que esto es un
first level exchange when the
exchange de primer nivel cuando el
volume comes from operating altcoins and
volumen viene de que operan altcoins y
not because of the volume of the main
no por el volumen de las principales
currencies ostias and being that it is well
monedas ostias y siendo que está muy por
below a binance friend eh No Hi
debajo de un binance amigo eh No Hola
guys before tomorrow's announcement, which
Chicos antes del anuncio de mañana que
is not even the most important announcement
ni siquiera es el anuncio más importante
for the token but it is quite
para el token pero sí que es bastante
important, I would like to clarify some
importante me gustaría aclarar algunas
things and some lies that the
cosas y algunas mentiras que los
usual criminals are
delincuentes de siempre se están
dedicating themselves to saying out there, basically I
dedicando a decir por ahí básicamente me
understand a totally pathetic and
entiendo una forma totalmente patética y
repulsive way, the funny thing is that they are
repulsiva la gracia es que están
simply raging because they are not
Simplemente rabiando porque no son
able right now to regain the
capaces ahora mismo de Recuperar el
control they had over the
control que tenían sobre el token de
pambi 1 token, they have completely lost it
pambi 1 lo han perdido por completo
thinking that I was going to abandon it
pensándose que lo iba a abandonar yo por
completely The token  It is true that I never
completo El token Lo cierto es que nunca
wanted to abandon it but I had the problem
Quise abandonarlo pero tenía el problema
that as you know there were people
de que como sabéis habían gente
specifically, especially a
específicamente sobre todo un
Venezuelan criminal who was
delincuente venezolano estuvo re
recently in prison. By the way, this is
entemente en prisión Por cierto esto es
too, too funny, this is
demasiado demasiado gracioso est esto es
fabric, this
tela esto
fabric, the fact that RAE is the only one who has been to
tela lo de que RAE sea el único que de
jail so far. I think it's
momento ha pisado la cárcel Me parece
spectacular. I was
espectacular estaba esperando
basically waiting to see how he could do the
básicamente para ver cómo podía hacer lo
same thing he did before, which is
mismo que hizo anteriormente que es
basically selling to
básicamente dedicarse a vender a todo el
everyone and basically stealing. In fact, he
mundo y a básicamente robar de hecho él
was the one to blame for Bitmart
fue el culpable de que en bitmart lo
delisting him as soon as he did so because he
delistar nada más se ló porque
stole all the money that
precisamente se robó todo el dinero que
I myself had put into the
yo mismo había puesto dentro del
exchange to be able to list it. As you
exchange para poderlo listar como
remember, it was 4,000 more, then another
recordáis fueron 4000 más luego otros
10,000 extra that I had to put in to be
10.000 extra que tuve que poner para
able to list again. The
poder volver aistar otra vez más bien el
issue of the rabble, this garbage that is
tema de la gentuza esta basura que está
dedicating itself to saying that about Oh, about because it
dedicando a decir lo de Ay lo del porque
is a scam, that is totally, you see
es una estafa eso es totalmente lo ves
here it says it is the second time that he
aquí dice es la segunda vez que se
withdrew and it was due to lack of liquidity, not
desista y fue por falta de liquidez no
because it is a scam, okay, look here they have
porque es estafa vale mira aquí tienen
a message from Bitmart that
un mensaje de bitmark
says here that it is for
en el que pone aquí que es por
liquidity, in other words, he has lied  again the
liquidez o sea ha mentido otra vez el
delox as if not Dallas is saying
delox como que no Dallas está diciendo
hbre d is not saying it he is
hbre d no lo está diciendo te lo está
telling you here
diciendo aquí
bitmark lie here Show several
bitmark mentira aquí Mostrar varios
messages from The group in which I am with
mensajes de El grupo en el que estoy con
bitmart the Group The one in which
bitmart el Grupo El que también estaba
this piece of Venezuelan criminal was also I
este pedazo de delincuente venezolano yo
simply allowed him to delist him
simplemente permití que lo deslistar
precisely so that he would think that I was
precisamente para que se pensara que no
never going to do anything more with the token
iba a hacer nunca Nada más con el token
and send everything to hell and he could not
y mandara todo al [__] y no podía
recover absolutely anything This was
recuperar absolutamente nada Esto fue
absolutely wonderful because
absolutamente maravilloso porque
basically this piece of sick man
básicamente este pedazo de enfermo
lost all control over the token and
perdió todo el control sobre el token y
as you can see the token right now is
como podéis ver el token ahora mismo es
much healthier right now yesterday you had
muchísimo más sano ahora mismo ayer tu
a 100% increase or in other words a [ __ ]
una subida del 100% o sea una [__]
madness but it still maintains itself with an
locura per todavía se mantiene con una
800% increase.  So the truth
subida del 800 por. Así que la verdad no
is not bad at all now what they are dedicated to
está nada mal ahora lo que se dedican a
saying is pretending that Bitmar
decir es a fingir que bitmar lo
delisted it for fraud And what do I know and it is
deslistada por estafa Y qué sé yo y es
all a total lie basically it was
todo totalmente mentira básicamente se
delisted because there was no liquidity left in
deslistado porque no quedaba liquidez de
fact the only liquidity that remained was
hecho la única liquidez que quedaba era
liquidity that had remained the reasons
liquidez que había quedado las razones
would be signs of fraud among other
serían indicios de estafa entre otras
things and it has 23 responses to the twt with
cosas y tiene 23 respuestas al twt con
2000 likes inside for the contract and
2000 likes dentro por el contrato y
also the one that I myself had
también la que yo mismo había puesto
originally put the token was Well
originalmente el token estaba Pues
basically essentially I met with
básicamente esencialmente me reuní con
the SEO of
el seo de
Bitmar dead at the time I
bitmark muerto en el momento en el que
made the announcement this is important to
hice el anuncio esto es importante
do because Well precisely so
hacerlo porque Pues precisamente para
that they would think that I was not going to do anything
que se pensaran que no iba a hacer nada
else with that token I was going to let it die
más con ese token lo iba a dejar morir
completely but I did not want to let it
por completo pero yo no quería dejarlo
die at any time but I have been
morir en ningún momento pero estado
silent during all this time
durante todo este tiempo callado
pretending that I was not going to do anything with it
fingiendo que no iba a hacer nada con él
but I did want to do something obviously I
pero sí quería hacer algo obviamente
never liked the idea of ​​​​leaving
Nunca me gustó la idea de dejar a todo
everyone abandoned without being able to give them
el mundo abandonado sin sin poderles dar
the second token because the second token was
el segundo token porque el segundo token
never worth anything And I said now is
nunca valió nada Y dije ahora sí que es
the good time for them to think that it is going
el buen momento que se piensen que se va
to  delist effectively delisted
a deslistar efectivamente se deslistado
Exactly the same as the first time this
Exactamente igual que por la primera vez
is the second time it's happened and then they're going to
ya es la segunda vez que ocurre y luego
list it again
lo van a volver a listar de todas
anyway because liquidity has
maneras porque la liquidez ha vuelto a
improved again and why did they completely lose
mejorar y para que perdían por completo
control what are they doing They are
El control para qué están haciendo Están
dedicating themselves to saying a bunch of
dedicando a decir un montón de payasadas
stupid nonsense talking about that if stff nonsense
estúpidas hablando que si stff payasadas
which doesn't make any [ __ ] sense because
cual no tiene ningún [__] sentido porque
literally all the m coins work
literalmente todas las m coins funcionan
exactly like this and there are thousands of mem coins
exactamente así y hay miles de mem coins
listed not only on bitmar but on a
listadas no solo en bitmar sino en un
bunch of different exchanges even on
montón de exchange diferentes hasta en
binance there are an awful lot of meme coins
binance hay una barbaridad de meme coins
and this makes them a scam It's not
y esto las hace una estafa No
just a speculative game dude he
simplemente es un juego especulativo tío
's completely stupid eh the delos eh I
es completamente tonto eh el delos eh o
mean But why does he continue why does he continue
sea Pero por qué sigue por qué sigue
making this fool of himself why doesn't he just stand
haciendo este ridículo porque no se pone
there and do his thing dude What need does he have, I
ahí a su rollo tío Qué necesidad tiene o
mean, the obsession eh be this type of
sea la obsesión eh sea este tipo de
obsession every time we've seen it
obsesiones cada vez que lo hemos visto
in someone who becomes obsessed with
en alguien que se obsesiona con alguna
someone these types of obsessions are the ones that
persona este tipo de obsesiones son las
in the end lead you eh to
que al final te llevan al fin eh a
lose everything because you focus
perderlo todo porque te centras
only on how you're terrible, how you
solamente en que estás fatal en que
're
estás
terrible  How many cases have we seen of
fatal Cuántos casos hemos visto de
people who have lost their
persona que se ha descentrado de su
way and are only focused on the
camino y solamente centrarse en la
obsession How many cases have we seen of
obsesión Cuántos casos hemos visto ya de
that with a need that impa H What
eso co necesidad que te impa H Qué
need do you have, isn't your
necesidad tienes no se supone que tu
girlfriend supposed to sue
novia va a demandar al
dalaxo in which, just like bitcoin,
dalaxo en el que pues igual que bitcoin
basically people buy something and
básicamente la gente compra algo y
simply wait a few years to see where it's going to be
simplemente espera unos años a ver dónde
at a certain moment in
va a estar eso en el cierto momento en
bitcoin for example, no team of
bitcoin por ejemplo noy ningún equipo de
absolutely anything, it's literally the
absolutamente nada es literalmente la
first mcoin that came out in the world, it is
primera mcoin que salió en el mundo está
as it is now, you all know, but
como está ahora todos sabéis pero
bitcoin intrinsically It's not that it
bitcoin de forma intrínseca No es que
has a functionality by itself,
tenga una funcionalidad de por sí
people simply buy it because they
simplemente la gente lo compra porque lo
want to buy it, it becomes popular and they
quiere comprar se hace popular y lo
follow it Javi Tomorrow I have a
sigen Javi Mañana tengo una entrevista
job interview wish me better of luck man, well, you
de trabajo deseame má suerte tío pues ya
tell us Come over and tell us about
nos cuentas Pásate y nos cuentas
buying Well, with pambi it's essentially
comprando Pues con pambi esencialmente
the same, it's the first mecoin that I released and tomorrow you'll see all the plans I have in this regard, I'm not even going to count all the plans, there's a better one, a couple more that I'm not going to count yet in
par más que todavía no cuento en el de
tomorrow's, but you'll see that it's going to be
mañana pero veréis que va a estar
too, too good, but yes,
demasiado demasiado bueno pero sí sobre
especially in this video I wanted to deny  a
todo en este video quería desmentir un
little bit to all these clowns these
poco a todos estos payasos estos
sick people who are trying to
enfermos que lo que están intentando es
do the same thing as always launching a
hacer lo mismo de siempre lanzar un
bunch of Food and in fact they are
montón de Food y de hecho se están
dedicating themselves to pretending that they have tokens they
dedicando a fingir que tienen tokens no
have nothing what they are trying to do is make
tienen nada lo que está intentando es
people
hacer que la gente
see or rather but r So this
ve o sea pero r Entonces ha dicho este
is Ren no that I have
es Ren no que a mí me quedaron
a lot of Pambi left and I am going to burst it
muchísimos pambi y lo voy a reventar
but of course or rather if I have it
pero claro o sea si lo tien de manera
illegally I do not sell so that if
ilícita no venda para que así Si la
people sell they can buy and then
gente vende ellos pueden comprar y luego
take more profit anyway they are
llevarse ellos más profit en fin son
clowns but it is really
unos payasos pero de verdad dan mucha
funny to see how they are dedicating themselves to
risa a ver cómo se están dedicando a
crying and saying a bunch of nonsense
llorar y decir un montón de tonterías
without any kind of sense and I knew
sin ningún tipo de sentido y yo sabía
that this was going to be like this again they
que esto iba a serer así de nuevo además
are also dedicating themselves to saying that we already knew
están dedicando a decir que ya sabíamos
that they were going to delist it of course why did they
que lo iban a deslistar claro por qué lo
know Well basically because Bitmar
sabían Pues básicamente porque bitmar
had been warning for a long time that they were going to
llevaba avisando un montón de tiempo que
delist them if the liquidity did not
iban a deslistar los si la liquidez No
improve Of course I wanted to
mejoraba yo Por supuesto que quería que
delist it obviously I wanted these
lo deslistar obviamente quería que esta
people to lose all control, to
gentuza perdiera todo el control lo
give it up for completely dead and
dieran por completamente muerto y no
have no control  some about the token and it's
tuvieran control alguno sobre el token y
very funny because they have literally
es muy gracioso porque literalmente no
achieved absolutely nothing but
han conseguido absolutamente nada pero
literally nothing the recession that it has
literalmente nada la recesión que ha
had is because it had a very large peak
tenido es porque tuvo un pico muy grande
yesterday obviously everything can't go up
ayer obviamente todo no puede subir
Eternally until infinity there always
Eternamente hasta el infinito siempre
have to be rises and then rises there
tiene que haber subidas y luego subidas
has to be a correction and then
tiene que haber una corrección y luego
there you can see what's going to
pues ahí se puede ver después lo que va
happen the truth is that I'm very
a pasar la verdad es que estoy muy
happy How things have happened is
contento Cómo han sucedido las cosas es
absolutely wonderful to go 40 steps
absolutamente maravilloso ir 40 pasos
forward and see them desperate
por adante y verlos desesperados
saying they have delisted pambi because it's
diciendo han deslistado pambi porque es
a scam it has nothing to do with it all
una estafa no tiene nada que ver todas
the m coins work Exactly the same it
las m coins funcionan Exactamente igual
's nothing more than a Ju of speculation and the
no es más que un Ju de especulación y la
majority well go to hell the
mayoría pues se van a la [__] la
funny thing is how ridiculous eh be the
gracia es que qué ridículo eh sea el
delo still has the podcast no I mean no lo lo
delo todavía tiene el podcast no O sea
deo it was there in
no lo lo deo fue ahí de
fact 100,000
hecho 100000
views or rather the fake reveal of nimo
vistillas o sea el fake reveal de nimo
putting Dallas in the
poniendo a Dallas en el
title has 5 days later 100,000
título tiene 5 días después 100.000
views has more like the tweet that you
visitas tiene más like el tweet que
visit the
visitas el
video has more likes likes likes
vídeo tiene más likes
has more likes the tweet that you
likes likes tiene más likes el tweet que
visit the video
visitas el vídeo
this one has changed the thumbnail me  I
a este le ha cambiado la miniatura me di
realized the other day that they put up
cuenta el otro día que aquí pusieron
like an audio here of
como un audio de
no this is the one that got a lot of
no este es el que le pilló un montón de
visits red
visit red
clear in fact I think elc still
claro de hecho creo que elc todavía
has some life look at these last ones they
tiene algo de vida mira estos últimos no
are not bad no
están mal no
130 60 that's not so
130 60 eso no tan
bad but it's because of that no because he gets together
mal pero es por eso no porque se junta
with the rep I don't know what ulti a
con el rep no sé qué ulti un
kiss But how [ __ ] up
beso Pero qué [__]
eh how [ __ ] up we still have some places
eh qué [__] nos queda algo lugares
[ __ ] But how embarrassing what about what to
[__] Pero qué vergüenza lo lo de que
go saying now that he talks to
ha ir diciendo ahora que habla con
him we still have some place over there or
el nos queda algo lugar por ahí o
what or we're going to
qué o vamos a
sleep at first he grabbed
mimir al principio agarraba
minions it's
miñones es
true it's
verdad es
true n what about Juan warn I'm putting it on
verdad n lo de Juan warn lo pongo en
Twitter now well people Hey
Twitter ahora bueno gente
today I recorded a video for the
Eh hoy he grabado un videíto para el
main channel What does Román say a kiss Alex
principal Qué dice Román un beso Alex
Ah It's
Ah Es
true Hey hey
verdad
hey in the debate Fernando said that he was
Oye oye oye en el debate Fernando dijo
going to
que iba a
Twitter that he was going to tweet the wallets he
Twitter que iba a twitear las carteras
had r Remember that You did
que tenía r Acuérdate de
n't finish watching the salsería
eso No terminaste de ver la salsería el
what What's
qué
up What have you put now come on
Qué pasa Qué habéis puesto ahora venga
what do you want what have you
qué queréis qué habéis
put what have you put man what do you
puesto qué habéis puesto
want me to see tell me  tell me
tío qué quieres que vea dímelo dímelo
straight what do you want me to see yes I've
directamente qué quieres que vea sí lo
seen it all
tengo todo visto
[Music]
[Música]
That I take no more I see you [Music]
That I take no
for
for
make cra
make cra
[Music] cinema cinema cinema cinema cinema
[Música]
absolutely
cine cine cine cine cine absolutamente
cinema guys
cine chicos
[Music]
[Música]
eh eye what's left what Tomorrow tomorrow
eh ojo que nos queda qué Mañana mañana
is the 26th of course tomorrow is the 26th and the day after We already have
es 26 claro mañana es 26 y pasado Ya
the premiere bye bye bye bye bye bye
tenemos el estreno bye bye bye bye bye
the teaser I would have liked I
bye el teaser me hubiera gustado me
would have liked to make a taser What
hubiera gustado hacer un taser Lo que
happens is that there's no longer time to make a
pasa que ya no no da tiempo a hacer un
teaser it's absurd anyway to
teaser ya es absurdo de todas maneras
make a teaser eh man no no it would be
hacer un teaser eh hombre no no estaría
good it would be good to make a teaser but no no no no no no
bien estaría bien hacer un teaser pero
the taser no
no el taser ya
no with what comes out we risk
no con lo que salga nos arriesgamos
no nothing but it's cinema man
no nada pero es cine tío
guys I'm going to
chicos me voy a
[Music]
[Música]
mimir and tomorrow will be another day
mimir y mañana será otro día
okay tomorrow will be another day protect
vale mañana ser otro día proteger
your Twitter accounts of
vuestras cuentas de Twitter de
encouragement
nimo
What this year I tried to
What este año intenté
help this year I tried to help a
ayudar este año intenté ayudar a una
person who told me that she was
persona que me contaba que la
mistreated and abused I didn't
maltrataban y abusaban de
even like her but I
ella ni siquiera me gustaba pero me
felt sorry and  I tried to get her out of the
sentí pena e intenté sacarla del
hell that
infierno que
the 27th said I'll tell you how she
decía el 27 os cuento cómo me lo
thanked me and everything she did to me since she's
agradeció y todo lo que me hizo ya que
looking for attention we'll
busca protagonismo se lo
give it to her another rewind another rewind
daremos otro rewind otro rewind
no
no
[ __ ] what will it
hostias qué
be let's see of course if she's telling me
será a ver claro que si me está diciendo
the
el
27th from here the 27th Ruben has regretted
27 de aquí el 27 Rubén se ha arrepentido
that
que
no I didn't even like him that's what
no ni siquiera me gustaba es lo que me
catches my attention
llama la atención
this year I tried to help a person
este año intenté ayudar a una persona
who told me that they mistreated her and
que me contaba que la maltrataban y
abused
abusaban de
her I didn't even like her but I
ella ni siquiera me gustaba pero me
felt sorry and tried to get her out of the
sentí pena e intenté sacarla del
hell that she
infierno que
said I didn't even like him
decía ni siquiera me gustaba
he was in a relationship but I think
él estaba en una relación pero creo que
with an
con una persona
anonymous person ví's sister threw one Indira
anónima la hermana de ví tiró una Indira
Auro you saw him villin's sister I don't know
Auro lo viste la hermana de villin no sé
and I don't know who
ni no sé quién es la hermana de
villin's sister is I've known her for many years I
villin la conozco hace un montón de años
didn't know he had a
no sabía que tenía una
sister man sou says why am I
hermana hombre sou dice por qué le doy
going around in circles because if he says he didn't
vueltas a pues porque si dice ni
even
siquiera me
like me it gives me the feeling that he's talking
gustaba me da la sensación de que habla
about a
de una
relationship but
relación pero
well if the 27th says something then
bueno si el 27 dice algo pues lo
we'll see Oh look I'll fix it
veremos Uy ya miren ya lo arreglaré
later there
después ya
was already  I'm not worrying,
hubo descuido
eh, let's go to sleep. I'm taking a look around.
eh vamos a mimir estoy echando un vistac
I'm up here to see if there's
Yo por aquí por lo alto a ver si hay
anything else, but I won't
algo más pero no
see you tomorrow.
nos vemos mañana
Handsome. See you tomorrow, handsome. Okay,
guapos nos vemos mañana guapos vale
rest and
descansad y